They smile in your face
While planning your fall
But the joke's on them now
I already read it all
It's run by those who see the design they lie they manipulate they play, but I learned the game yesterday
Never fight with your innocent
I'm already finished while you're still starting This isn't a battle, it's a foregone conclusion
You can throw stones, but I'ma still ache Every ripple you make just shows where you break
Can't comprehend what you can't see Can't begin what I've already pensied
Isn't defeating your ass
So Poison Z, yeah, that I breathe
I don't believe in friendship anymore
Dackers in my co-
But CO2 is the only truth we've got.
Confucius says hi. It's male. We got Jamie's Cowboys. We got
Is my is male
I smile I smile twig boy less
Or you're just or you're just easy
Hmm
Yeah, how's your day going?
Oh god
Confucius says, Confucius say, eat a fortune cookie.
Hello, Nor.
Nor, you're at your butthole, please.
Oh, my God.
Nor.
You're just moving the chat.
Hi.
Confucius said, oh, you're sitting there.
This is the post that it was like, here's a poll.
It said, what's more important?
Somebody's child or a terrible pet owner
or something like that.
Of course, the human child one.
I'm thinking about that terrible pet owner.
But anyway, it's not a contest.
Oh my God, who's worth?
It's also, but it's so funny seeing like these
like ecotistical people
Thinking that they can tell everybody where they can go and what they can oh and nobody better be in there
We're gonna be like, you know going after anybody that's in there
Are you if I know Barry's afraid he wrote me instead of Kate will Kate said she's gonna kill me and not know
I can you know, and he said he's afraid of her, but I'm
I blocked him because I know he's just you know beating her information. So I refuse spies, but I'm
Yeah, I buried Barry you're exhausted late tonight late nights. Yeah
Yeah, I mean, it's like
Hey, I mean there's a reason like you know, I
Don't know he's like he's like whoa Sam man has a picture of my my dick in a pocket pussy
Well, that's what happens when you send a picture of your dick to Sam man. He's gonna say that he's gay
I look like the Crip Keeper. Hold on one second. What does that say?
Where do these happy meals go when you eat them?
I'd better not be throwing them up.
Excuse me.
Did you just say to me?
First of all, I don't eat happy meals.
I make, I don't like, I think they're wasting money.
So I get like, you know, actually like, I mean,
I got a real, I mean, I guess I had McDonald's,
I had a burger and fries, but I didn't get a happy meal.
But anyway, and so then,
I mean, I bet it's like, I mean, it's like, and then she's like, oh my God, oh, he thinks
that Kate's, Kate's telling people not to go there, isn't it stupid?
But literally, I heard her say that tonight, like, I heard, I actually heard her say that,
oh, and I heard Tripp and Sips say it, I heard RG say it.
Oh, God, they'll never be back.
Oh, no.
But, oh my gosh, they will be here.
They don't want anybody else to be here.
All they're gonna do is sit here
and look at who's coming to the chat.
Oh my god, and there's a bunch of little
butt lickers of theirs that are gonna be like,
well, not of him, but, and then, oh my gosh.
And Bita said, I might not be allowed on her panel anymore.
Can you imagine?
Oh no, my life is over.
Oh, her piano was one of the highlights of my life.
You know, I just got abused up there
and, you know, ganged up on and called terrible things.
Hey, I don't need to be sitting there
and yell terrible things.
I can do it on my own show.
But WFC, where are you eat?
Does that mean where the fuck did I eat?
WFC, what is WTFC, I don't know.
I don't know what it means, Jamie, I'm not sure.
What the fuck did I eat?
I had McDonald's.
I'm just kidding.
I don't know what that is.
Oh.
Oh, the norm.
But anyway, yeah, who the fuck cares?
I mean, it's like really, I mean, it's like, these are like,
and it's like, who cares who in this community?
And that's not, I mean, this community,
it's not my community.
It's like really like their communities.
Who cares?
I don't want their communities here.
Like that are more loyal to them and stuff like that.
They're not my people. They're just like they're basically their spies and they're followers
I have my own cult members and I don't I don't like raise followers
That's why no one's really allowed in the cult except for like me and like my daughter and Lenore and
You know, Alexander's the high priestess. Hey, hey, hey, what's up to see you girl. Um, yeah
I am I would never tell anybody where to go or what to do. It's like I'm just I'm just happy that your people are here
But it's like I don't like people being bullied
because somebody else is mad, and it's like all these people are so imperfect. These are all
doxers. They've all gone after each other, done illegal fucking shit, like a lot of it.
Right, they all do illegal fucking shit. Oh, why doxer? Oh, they all dox each other
They all do all doing this shit
And if you don't know about that about it they're doing I'm having the scenes most of the time around right and Kate Kate actually has a little bit of
Self-awareness and was admitting that she has done bad things, but she was a beta today
I'm like I'm also apologizing ready to hate bond with beta and stuff like that. Maybe that's what I did with her a little bit
Overbeat. I mean, I was like, you know, sometimes we can be careful about
while we bond because it's like those are like kind of like a really fragile bonds
Christine looks like she has shredded wheat on her head yeah exactly hold on I think that's
the comment of the day I think I think you're in a mod for that comment Lez okay
and also because Christine can't stand you so that means you're okay in my book I'm just kidding
I just like you for you. I'm not trying to
Yeah, but it's okay. So Kate's over there and then Sam is like, okay, you you were sucking his dick
Oh my god. Hey, Sam and you're over here sucking my dick almost every night. I mean, what are you talking about?
I don't even want my dick sucked by you anymore, Sam and you have you
You know your your gap in your teeth is
scraping my wiener
Like leave it alone. I don't want it. Let it go. Don't don't touch it anymore. Stay away from it
Not gay. Well, I'm gay, but not for statement. Hey, Dr. Manhattan. I am banned and bans a few people just a few people
Yep, come gap. Oh my god, Lava
Does that mean oh, yeah the come gap. Yeah, and this teeth
Yeah, and I think I mean I was actually funny part of Kate's tonight. I watched a little bit of her show
She had it. She had this like guy. There's like adult man like
Buying like thousands of Eugeo cards. Okay guys, you know, that's where the money is going
It's going to Eugeo cards all them all those donations for I mean it big played about me
I'm gonna feed the cats and eat. He's buying Eugeo cards
So you have boxes full of these fucking kids game cards and oh, it's easy money
You're addicted to the cards not not even the not even the money at this point. It's like beanie baby people
It's like, oh, yeah, they're even worth something someday
Yeah, I mean, those those markets are all it's all here we go. Hold on one second
I'm just gonna do a few things. Okay and
You okay?
Here we go. Okay. Okay, but
WFC like the WWF
Okay
Okay, so let me see
Jamie, he does have a beautiful soul.
Hi, Lava, how are you?
Yeah.
Okay.
What's Oh My God about?
Yeah.
Don't make Twig a mod.
He mods with his feelings.
Less?
Well, don't you, Dr. Manhattan,
don't you like it a little bit?
Kesty sometimes.
But if you don't,
but if you guys, I did mod some people,
but if you don't want the mod, I understand.
You're welcome.
Yeah.
No, thank you. Thank you for being here and being a friend
Because I mean at this point the guys it is like there are gonna be people that are like afraid of these like you know loud mouths and
And they're gonna get probably get yelled at them by them and like you know, maybe kicked out of their chats and stuff like that
That's just sucks. You're chill. Okay. I think you're chill too. That's why I don't know how you got hit him
But I am hate you because I was like no doctor Manhattan. I always need a doctor. I like to have a man
I need a prostate exam and a your analysis
So yeah, there we go.
So I'm just kidding, I'm too young for prostate exams.
And I don't think are you are you a real doctor or are you one of those mad scientists at the doctors either way?
You give me a prostate examine people now. I'm just I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry. Oh my god
I knew his big phony is that guy NorCal and then there's this person that was their name
I mean she has like almost like she's almost cool her new kitten cakes or something. She's like, oh my god
He was lying about NorCal NorCal is the biggest fucking piece of shit in the world. I mean, it's like okay NorCal over there
Oh, he's like just slandering me for like two hours on the panel. Oh, say all these things. Oh, he's not a good interviewer
He's not I mean they're just saying this bullshit that it's like not even true, right? Yeah
You're about to be timed out soon. Well, let's don't time them out. Okay
Um, yeah, I don't like I mean so yeah, but I'm pretty much I'm like I don't want followers. I want
To create leaders, you know, I want to like, you know inspire people to do their own channels
I want to like help people with their channels. I I don't want to be a
This like, you know, this like they're trying to turn me into some kind of negative force and trying to paint me with all kinds of stuff
Like that are other people. Thank you. Yeah. Thank you. Thank you very much. I mean
Yeah, that's what I think a lot of people don't understand. I think I'm a clown. I think I'm just dumb. I think I'm
don't know they think I'm I don't know what I'm doing and sometimes I don't
sometimes I just like let myself go and I don't really think about things which
is kind of fun sometimes listen yeah yeah you hear that nerd boy it less has
I give I give less like a pair of glasses it wasn't money for 20 how are you
hey Sipha how are you good to see you it's been a little bit good to see you
Yeah, but I mean it beat us today. Like she's like, oh, well, you know, I'm not I don't think I'm gonna have them on the panel anymore
I but she's but she's nothing she she will I mean she's it doesn't sound like she's very
And it's like guys it's like anything that they're accusing me of right now or even him is like
Everybody's attached to people like that. I mean everybody made everyone wants to say oh this person is worse. This person is worse
No, I mean it's like all pretty much the same kind of bullshit charges
You is nothing like
Most of the time it's not even criminal charges
It's just like oh they were on the internet and they made like a little little slip up on the internet
And then everyone's just gonna jump on there on their necks forever because they're just trolls. Oh
There's ice agent. That's big. So big tall sexy Rob. Yeah money money money. Yeah
Money, money, money's in here.
Don't donate to him to freeze him out.
Well, why would people want to freeze me out
when it's like I'm actually entertaining?
I mean, I think, I mean, it's like,
I mean, I'm not saying that they're not
or they don't have their own,
their own, you know, people that like them.
And I don't, I'm not discouraging anybody to do anything.
I'm not, I don't tell you what to do.
Who are they to tell you what to do?
Who are they?
Oh, we're gonna, nobody better do, nobody better donate to them or anything.
You better not be in here looking, looking to see who's in here.
I mean, they better not, I mean, they better not be like,
because they're, they're in here for sure.
They know everything that goes on in my show.
They're playing by clips.
They're, oh, look how good he looked a year ago.
I know I've been dealing with you motherfuckers for a year.
Of course I aged 10 years in a year.
Look what I've been dealing with you.
Not you, but them.
Persian spells and you know goblin magic from Shrek or whatever the go over or goblin whatever the fuck
He is lucky. I'm not a donkey at this point. You make more your Lopez look tiny. I'm lucky
I'm not I actually even like even when she may be a donkey, which was kind of like a where's money's wrench
He lost it because he told me
He was making fun of my nails and stuff and I don't like it. So it's okay. I mean, it's okay. I mean, they're clean
I mean relatively tonight, but um
And then he unmodded me too, but he can still be in the chat, he's fine, I mean I respect him as a channel.
Mario Lopez is small, gosh, I had a crush on him.
You're trying to help me, well, you haven't got as much tact as, like, I don't know.
It's them. I'm sorry. Okay. It's fine. It's fine. You don't even know you don't need to be a mod. Yeah
Yeah, who cares?
I'm a modern Stephen King's shirt. That's about all I need, right? You got to get money back in the loop
Okay, well, maybe when he wants to buy me
You know, maybe you can buy a wrench from me. I mean, I probably start selling them for $20 a piece
Yeah, thank you. I know he's not a POS
Even though he did like, you know jump over return style and get maced in the subway
Even though that happens. It's okay. I'm not judging him
Alexander McQueen sitting there with his like four even Alexander McQueen whatever people say about him
He's sitting there with his four quarters or eight quarters. He doesn't need one. He doesn't even care now
He's gonna be queen sits there and puts women at a time and go
Money just jumps over it every day
It's crazy. It's okay
It's kind of like me me getting my free my free refills of coffee sometimes, but hey, sometimes I need it
Like hey, we're like on YouTube trying to make a living and then nobody wants us to be successful
Like the only reason most people donate is so they can say oh
You're doing me to donators
It's like so stupid. I mean it's like that but then whenever whenever they make the bands and stuff
Oh my god, you're blocking donate. Yeah. Yeah, Jamie is very loyal, which I do appreciate. I do know you pay tax
I know you pay taxes, but that's not
I mean, yeah, I can pay taxes too, but, you know, that doesn't mean I can go, you know, jump over the subway turnstile if there was a subway here, I don't know.
But, I don't know, I'm not judging you. Hey, hey, I took my old cup and I got this free coffee.
I think the guy, I think someone reported me to the bagel shop, but I don't think that's me.
I don't care. I don't care. They don't care. It's like the fucking they throw it out. They throw out the coffee
Anyway, what do they care? And I'm a good customer. Anyway, I buy other stuff all the time
So you're not gonna be like, oh my god, so when called it said you're getting free refills
It says free refills. How much caffeine do I drink a day? I have one. I have two of these
I have this one. I have this one. I drink
One already today. I have a beer and I
I got I got a nice I got a really good gift today though. I got and I'm gonna
thank whoever sent beautiful gift I love you chocolate cover strawberries and I
have a like a strawberry chocolate but yeah I have a I have this one copy to
actually these two copies and I have an alcohol
300 milligrams. Well, if I think any one cup of coffee, there's about a hundred milligrams, right?
So yeah, probably about 300 to 500 milligrams. I do when I don't drink coffee for a day or two. I start getting a bad
It's like I don't really I don't I can drink I can go without alcohol, but if I go without coffee, I'll get a headache
Yeah, but
I mean, it's like really there's like so much judgment going on and I listen to these people talk about me
I didn't say anything in the chat or anything. I was just like I just kind of like to see it Chanel
How are you sweetheart? I like to see like what's being said and stuff like that and it's just like
Sam ends like, oh my God, you're doing this.
And Sam ends is the same thing.
I mean, it's like, who is he to judge me?
But I mean, it's like, at least Kate had the,
had the self-knowledge to know.
Yeah, she's like, I'm not perfect.
She's like, I, she's, she's, I mean, she's fucked up.
It's just, she understood I'm not perfect either.
And it's like, you know, and maybe I've given her
a second chance too at times too.
And I was nicer too.
And maybe she didn't approach me to the right way
about some certain things.
And maybe other people may deserve second chances too.
You don't like the WWE energy drinks?
What, like that Logan Paul shit?
That's just, that's just disgusting.
What's it called?
I don't know, it's that terrible,
I don't even want to say the name of that drink.
I don't know, it's like piss water.
Oh my God, remember when they made those Lunchables meals
and they had KSI and Logan Paul?
Oh my God, it was so dorky.
Yeah, and look at like they're making
People are so weird. It's like so he's literally making like, you know, his brother is doing 25 million dollars to like throw a fight with my Tyson
And then people are upset if I get like a dollar or something like that. I mean, it's like it's just like
It's so so weird. It's like, oh, well
His family is that anything you know about my family. They think I know anything about me. It's like it's just like they're just wrong
And it's really none of their business too, but it's like I really I'm gonna start asking for all these people that this a shit like this
I'm gonna start asking for their tax returns for their criminal records and for their ID
I need all this information if they're so interested in my information
I should get all their information too, right? It's just just fair
They also should go on camera and do a show too,
instead of just sitting and a lot of most of these people
just sit in chats and judge people.
Probably, probably.
Guys, can you imagine?
Okay, maybe I'm a little bit messy.
These people are probably like, you know,
500 pounds and just squalor and just sitting there
behind them, because they're literal trolls,
most of these people, like literal trolls.
like they look like the troll dolls.
And then they're sitting judging people like, you know,
me who looks like this like fucking, you know, king.
Anyway, you're 360 pounds, well, that's okay.
I mean, I can care.
I mean, I don't, hey, you're 360 pounds of love
as far as I'm concerned.
But it's like, I'm sure you're, you know,
if you're in this chat, there's a reason like, you know,
you like the, you know,
at least you're trying to do better for yourself.
So.
Um, well, maybe I hope so I'm I'm really into self-improvement and I never said I was perfect, but um
You know
And I'll talk some shit, but it's like they are fucking judgmental. I'm not saying don't go to their chat
I'm not saying. Oh, I'm not gonna have I mean I like fucking
I promoted most of these people.
I mean, I've like let them on my panel for hours and hours,
but barely a thank you or like basically they feel entitled
that I got clumsy came in the other day,
he's like, how dare you block me?
And they're just crying over it.
It's like, well, you're saying horrible things to me
on my show.
Like, why do I need to put up with that?
I don't understand.
Like, why?
Yeah, well, I dated a heavy set woman.
She's probably 250 pounds
About um, that was enough. I think I know I don't know I think I'm uh
I'm uh
You know, but heavy people give the best hugs though. No, they do
They do it feels they feel so nice and squishy. I'm just I'm so sorry. Oh
My god, sweetie. I mean it's like if you read the chats
These chats are just ridiculous. Oh, they're saying. Oh, I'm sure he's there's like
Speculating. Oh, I know for a fact a hundred percent. He's getting money from this person. He's a pays his pay pig
Pay pig
What are you talking about? I barely made five dollars this month. I mean, it's like Jesus. I mean, I don't understand
They're just like pay pig
I need some pay pigs.
I mean, does anybody know?
I get them over here right away.
What are they talking about?
I don't even think they're paying a big idiot.
I mean, God, I don't expect any.
It's like, geez, it's like, I'm happy when people,
when people do donate in it,
it's like, I know I'd pay for a lot of stuff
and I like Mexican men and you're taking anyways,
you're Samoan.
What a shame.
Oh, you are 360 pounds.
But I think you're like more like six foot or like five foot nine or something not you're not six seven
I don't think maybe you are
This is is this your mom right here? Hold on. I just want to ask a question. I think I have this picture
I'm just this is either sick or it might be your mom. Have you seen this picture right here? Oh
No, I can't bring it up anymore
I don't have that premium stream yard.
See, I can't even afford fucking stream yard anymore.
It's a broke I am lately.
I mean, I don't even have the pictures of it safe.
Oh my God, terrible.
Okay, well, I was gonna show a picture
of a Simone woman, just picture Stig.
He basically looks like a Simone woman.
Closest that you're gonna get around here, I think.
Anywho, let me see.
Yeah, so I'm thinking I'm gonna be
Probably I think I've spent a lot. I think I spent like I think I just like I'm like two available here all the time
Like I'm like two I just do too much and it's like people just kind of take me for granted
So I'm thinking of like kind of cutting back my hours. Maybe just doing like three days a week
No mamas no ma- no memes. No Mamys. My mamys. My mamys. My mamys. I don't know what that means
Is that Spanish? You said you're not Mexican. Oh, okay. Oh, yeah, I can look one second
But if it's asking about, well, let's look.
OK.
Well, let me see.
Sure.
Sure, Jamie.
Sure, sure, sure.
OK.
Grab a heap.
Perfect.
I'll do it.
I'll do it when I can.
OK.
You got it.
Yeah.
Actually, I did make a really good,
hey, what's up, everybody?
I did make a really good scene,
and I think we'll have better.
Better energy with less of these like some of less of these people that are just like such followers and like and just basically
They're like, oh my god, like it's like I'll miss their presence
I'm like they've ever done anything except been rude to me and and you know talked shit about me
Am I gonna miss them? No, I hope they go away
I mean, it's like geez like there's so many people that I really could not give a fuck if I never see them again
But no, I love you guys but it's like
So many of these people that I just be talking as like, oh, they're just talking that we're shit. It's like
Oh, it's just like I was like I'm not I'm like just like thank God. I'm not them like sitting there like you know
And it's like
Maybe
Thank you so much as males. Thank you so much. I did really I did make a really good video today
Um, and I wanted to show when there's more people in the chat, so I'll show you this one
It's pretty it's pretty good one
I think I'm trying to try to do this Machiavelli series where I'm kind of like educating on like the work to Machiavelli
Who I think is a pretty brilliant political strategist and
understands power and dynamics and things like that and and how you know things really work and so
I do
I mean, it's like, is that one?
Let's see.
Off my channel. I'm sick. You'll like this. I just did this today. I got a lot of likes and so I think that people do like it
it's
One of my better ones, okay, so oh
Yeah, and also people don't people understand Capricorns. You don't understand it's like
This you if Capricorns could probably understand but
Capricorns don't like just give up, you know, it's like or just they don't just sit down and like, you know
Just like let themselves be abused, you know
So but anyway, this is called standing alone
It's really good. I hope you enjoy it and I'll be right back
They didn't shout, they didn't fight, just rewrote you out of sight, little whispers, subtle shifts, truth got buried under myth.
A moment clipped to feelings, one half a story, now it's done, people follow what they feel, not always what is real.
They needed you to pay the part, react, defend, fall apart, but you stepped out of the frame.
Now they don't control the game, patterns break, they lose their hold, can't predict
you like before.
I'm happy I cleared out half the room.
Thank you so much.
I'm happy I cleared out half the room
because it's just people are like,
oh, yeah, they're like so stupid.
They don't know that,
they don't know like the wisdom
that are putting in this and like the messages.
And it's like, I'm glad that you guys are getting them,
but it's like, I'm just glad they're leaving.
I'm like, and they think that I care.
RG, Tripp, Zip, B, I mean, I was like,
and they're all watching anyway.
I mean, they just pass forwards, but they have to watch.
They're addicted.
I heard, like, what's that guy's name?
That stupid idiot, NorCal.
He's like, oh, well, you know, I love, I like,
Robert, he's like, I'm addicted to, like, psyche.
You know, he's like insane, and Sam is addicted.
He's like, they're all like a bunch of addicts over there,
like, oh, psyche, psyche, psyche.
All they just can do is talk about me, and I say,
oh, man.
Oh, man.
It's like they're just obsessed with like, I mean, I mean, I'll mention them for like right now, but they talk about me the whole show.
I mean, it's like, and then it's like, and then it's like, but they, and then it's like, and then on Cal's like, oh, well, you know, I just like to see him crash out and I like to trigger him and like, you know, and he's funny when he does that like blah, blah, blah.
I'm funny even when I don't crash out.
I know I'm funny.
Okay.
I'm glad I'm glad you get, you know, you find it funny because it's supposed to be funny.
You know part of being an actor, but anyway, no
And most of the time they're 90% genuine, but sometimes I exaggerate a little bit for comedic effect, but who cares it's like
At least I don't say shalulu
Man, how annoying I'd be if I don't know it's like basically as I someone these people
I can't understand why people like how they can listen to it. It's like, thank you
Sam, oh, Sam is just so, oh, and it's like, he's like,
oh my God, he was like, he was screaming about Kate
and he's like, okay, you're a suckin' socks dick.
And she's like, I wasn't sucking his dick.
She wasn't in the beat us chat.
And it's like, and so she's even in beat us chat.
I mean, it's like, these people, wow.
I mean, it's like, do you think that Rudy likes the catnip?
I know he loves catnip.
Let's see, let me see Rudy right there.
Rudy's always sitting there. Lenore, you're sitting over there? Oh, my table.
Lenore, where are you? Right there.
And Lola's been around. Okay.
And we have Rudy likes catnip.
Remember how he would just start rolling around and stuff? Yeah, he's over there.
We had a really fun night last night with we had Alexander on and Alex McQueen and we had
Like a bunch of people up on the panel
I kind of ended it because then they started I started speaking Italian with them with that guy
It's uncomfortable because they're they're like saying swears and Italian. I thought they were talking about me
so I just like said, okay
mending it and
You know Italian is basically just a bunch of curses like the language. It's just basically like
Basically very similar to Spanish and French, but with like it's all curses
It's like it's all it's like all swear words, and it's like I think you can curse people with that language
I think it's like a that's why it's a boot that like that shape like a boot. It's like it's like a kind of like
And that's why they have like the most evil like organizations in the world over there because
It's like it's like a it's a very witchy place. Well, even like Medusos
Or your ace agents twin brother. Hey, do you know where the guy the guy that tried to assassinate Trump?
You know, he's from where I was born like the city called Torrance
It's a neighboring city over here, but it's a kind of big news over here
Like see who's a tutor or something around here
And I like his I like his mugshot. He's like this
He's like has a smirk on his face
And then like he and he called Trump a PDF, which is kind of funny, but it's I mean, it's not funny
but it is funny yeah, and
And Trump is like, oh my god. He's oh my god
So shock. It's like
It's like do people understand what the main out of people being called these names
It's like they don't really mean anything to anybody anymore
And it's like and nobody can even joke about anything that and now it's like instead everyone takes everything so seriously
It used to be a time when like, I mean, where people had teachers, like, you know, students
had, I can't even believe it's like, like people under the age of 18 still have adult
teachers.
I'm just, I'm just surprised because I mean, think about how difficult that would be.
Like all these, I think it's all going to be chat GPT teachers pretty soon.
Like it's going to be, that's going to be the teachers because it's like, everyone's
going so crazy about, you know, oh my God, like everyone, like my child's going to get
S8 if they if they go to school and stuff like that. Hey Charisma, how are you? I saw Charisma sticking up for me today and say
She's Charisma said so I'm usually look in the mirror and I agree with that so much because I just like
and then Sam was like
Well
I'm sure she would enjoy like looking in the mirror more than he would because you see that some toothless
freak
Sam and Wood, I personally see a lovely, beautiful woman.
So, I mean, jeez, you're, I know, I don't want to hear,
I don't want to hear about the Chip and Dale, please.
Calabas, Calabas, this talk's strong.
Yeah, I heard that story never had a mugshot that would definitely flex your muscles
No, like they they won't leave flex your muscles and much. I know I try to smile in my one of my mugshots
And they told me not to smile. They're like don't smile that a pair of silts and got to smile on hers
So I smiled in mine, and I said don't smile. Oh
I don't like that. That's a really bad mugshot
But uh, yeah, but unfortunately in California
There's like some privacy thing where they don't share them with everybody else or else. They would be all over the internet
But yeah, I
Mean everyone like people understand we're not perfect as human beings
We all make mistakes and like what if like, you know, and
Like what if like, you know, just like this community will just latch on to anything and then they say
It's like they think that they're perfect or something. They're a bunch of trolls
Like they're like the worst almost like the scum of the earth a lot of these people
Like really and it's like
They're not even like good trolls. They're just like they're like equal like the like under they're like under the bridge type of trolls
right, it's like
with all their Wi-Fi is from McDonald's, stuff like that.
They're like the worst kind of troll.
I'm like troll royalty, where I was like,
I'm not even really a big troll,
but I know about it because I have royal trolls
in my background.
These people are like, just common gutter trolls.
It's like, all they say is just bullshit.
And this he-man person, watch out for this person.
This person's a big fucking loudmouth.
What is troll?
Well, you're one.
See that little face you make and and your comments. That's that's a you're like a gutter troll, but it's okay
I like you you're fine. I'm trying to get you to raise up a little bit
Yeah, I mean money for 20 it's like you and I it's like the thing is money for 20 is like very like a
chameleon kind of thing
Like where he like he just likes to he like is like nice wherever he goes and stuff like that like so
But yeah, it's like he's kind of kissing their butts a little bit and it's like
So it's just maintain your independence a little bit there's a lot of people that want to use you for your platform and stuff
You'll understand like the longer you go. You'll see how nice I looked, you know
How happy I was a year ago and like now it's a year later
You can see I've aged like 10 years you'll understand I guess you're going through it already
I was as nice as you were I was very nice. I started out not nice anymore. I
Mean it's like if I was I would be just I'd be consider myself kind of brain dead because it's like
After what I've been through with this shit. Oh my god
Oh, I mean, it's just like I've been through everything but yeah, anything that is how are you?
But yeah, he's not a bad guy
420 is not a bad guy, but it's like I do see a little bit of the butt kissing kind of that's okay
It's I mean it's like
Yeah, just just kind of kiss mine by a little bit more. You know, I don't you would never tell be the you know
Oh, here's a $2 for your nails or whatever
I'm sure even if you're trying to be helpful and it really wasn't very helpful. Okay, you're okay. Are you just okay?
It's going on thing that is what's happening tonight
We did you enjoy last night's show it was some shocking revelations. Yeah, we had a thing
We weren't we haven't beat us yet this morning. I don't know it's just a lot of yeah
I think that he's I know the Persian spell. I think you know
I I got that out of my system pretty quickly people think I'm still under it, but no I
I
Had to get a exorcist last year about April so it's been about a year. It's been off of me
Actually, right after I got that tattoo,
basically that shocked me out of it.
You think my nails are good?
Well, they're not perfect tonight,
but they're better tonight.
Thank you so much here.
They're a little bit better than I had to take a nice bath,
try to scrape out one of them.
I do like scrape out tobacco and stuff.
And I mean, NorCal was like,
oh my God, he doesn't have any self-awareness
because look, anybody that would pop fleas, okay, well.
He's never heard of like combing fleas off of cats like a flea comb
You're the strongest man and sexy man ever
Exists and you're not trolling little fella
Well, I've seen your picture again
You're not this strongest nor sexiest man. You're kind of balding
You look you look kind of more Mexican than Samoan too. I was picturing like the rock and I got the pebble
You know, but it's okay. It's okay. You know, you're still not a bad person or bad troll, whatever you are
But no, I still like you I split. Oh
Okay, okay. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. Oh, he's a nice person. I see I said, you know, JT JT talks to you
anyway
You gotta be careful about camming up because if you do cam up you're it's out there. Yeah
You send me you sent me a fake picture
And it wasn't something you sent to me. It was something that JT took your picture when you're backstage on a stream yard
And then he posted on his community wall. Did you know that?
It was a long time ago that he did that
Sorry sorry to inform you I've seen I've seen your real picture
I've seen most of people's real pictures too because
Fortunately, I do have people that send me things
But Barry sent me a picture of his dick and his butt. I don't even think it was his and so he just sent me fake things
That's why I had unfriendly but he also he didn't say Samman has a picture of his dick in a pocket pussy and his butt as well
And he said and Samman download it
Why why would you even give him the opportunity don't send that out to Samman then of course, he's gonna download it
He's gay. I mean, it's like I don't know people just don't make much sense, you know
Why why is your eyes open so big thing that is I think that's what he said
That's what Barry said. He said I had my dick in a pocket pussy and say man has it and you think he had homo
Barry stop sending your dick pics and your butt pictures to people. I'm glad I didn't get a real one
I think I think he gave me like a more famous porn stars
It was a really weird looking penis that he sent me. It was kind of like half white and it's like what is this an Oreo cookie?
I don't know. Yeah, he took a picture of it and he sent it to Sam and then Sam man has it
And he's now he's complaining
Take a Sam man has it. Well, he said that to him. I mean, why would he even send it to him? Oh, you see Ivoris, okay
Yeah
Like that's what he said.
I mean, he said it on Kates tonight.
He was sitting on Kates and he has,
I think he has a new website called,
I think he stole Samman's phrase,
which is pack it up or something like that.
It's like a pack it up clip show or whatever.
He's trying to be a clipper now.
So I don't know, who cares?
I just want to make Don's happy be able to,
I don't want to buy fucking Eugeo cards or fucking, you know.
I mean, I just want to eat sometimes, you know, it's like, I mean, it's like, so anyone wants to like, you know, I've opened up my, my, my, my banner, it's not like anybody, well, a few people, some people do help me.
I do appreciate you, but I would love to like, you know, I'm doing readings, I have my cards here.
If anyone wants a nice long reading, we can do long, nice long reading.
I'll be watching my thing, but it's like, I know it's like, sometimes it's like, I don't want to like.
Oh my God, let me see what's happening.
Let me see.
So any takers, we'll see.
Hey, yeah, your hair is balding.
Yes, it's like kind of like black
and it's like kind of really thin up top, really thin.
He will be happy.
Yeah, I will be happy.
How about, so everyone, if you can cash out me,
is that gonna give you the happy meal?
You're winning?
Okay.
Yeah, so there. Okay. Let me see. I'm gonna keep my eye on this phone tonight. Okay
So anyway, I will do free readings too, so if anyone wants a free reading, I'll just do a few cards for you and
then if anyone would like a
Song I can
Do some songs there. Oh, this was good guys. This this this live I did the other night remember when I was playing that um
I was playing that Groucho Marks show and then the stream ended and I got a warning that night and I appealed it and
My appeal was granted so yay
So that's kind of a relief a little bit
So
Because it was fair use. I mean it's like I was commenting on it and we were all talking and laughing and stuff
You're talking and laughing and stuff
Ah
Yes
Thank you, okay
Okay, yeah, you yeah, then let me read your future guys. Okay somebody who wants to answer reading. Let's see
I'll just do like I'm just and if you I mean, I said I'll just do one to three cards whatever for free if you want like a 10 card reading I will
Five to ten dollar donations perfect for that or any song you want I'll play but yeah, I did get you
You look who looks like Bert from Bert and Ernie LD he does he does kind of look like Bert and Bert and Ernie
It's interesting. I never thought of that before
Well, he's a little bit cuter than that, but it's so funny, like, like, then, you know,
LD had controversy too, and it's like, and Bita still has him on her show, but Bita was telling
me last year, don't have him on your show. And it's like, I guess she went to war with her chat
over and stuff. For like, it was like, for the dumbest thing I don't know. He was doing a panel
It's not like it's not like a five-year-old child went on the band. I was like, you know, 16 or 17 or 18 year old girl
I don't know but somebody came on and maybe flash or something like that
I don't know then all of a sudden it's like he's like considered like some kind of like, you know
Grape is I mean it's like it's so so stupid how people are like how cuckoo for cocoa puffs people are you understand that
There's actually real people that are hurt and like really like, you know, like
This horrible physical assault are happening and they're worried about shit that happens on YouTube and what people are watching on YouTube and stuff
It's like that's how stupid our society is. It's kind of like
It's like down every turning it's turning those things into meaningless things
And it's like and it's also just hurting like the real cases of actual things and putting all this attention on this bullshit
Plus there's anybody that would be forgiven. I think it's for stupid shit on the internet. It's like, you know, no one's like really it's like
There's so much of this saturating it.
It's like, I mean, it's like the real sick thing is like,
there's people that like, people called the cappers
that would actually like extort teenagers and stuff like that.
And those are the kind of people that these people are.
I mean, I'm not saying that they do that,
but it's like there's the same kind of like
evil troll kind of thing where they like celebrate
people's deaths and stuff like that,
which is like something that these people would do, right?
Crystal Marina's saying some sick shit the other night.
Oh, I mean, I was talking about somebody,
this guy basically didn't really do anything.
He's just, you know, make some stupid jokes.
And then she's like, oh, he needs to have his like, no,
you know, his eyes taken out and disfigured and tortured.
It's like, what the fuck?
All right, what the fuck?
It's like, really, and it's like,
and that's acceptable behavior.
It's like that, and they're like, yay, yay.
It's like, okay, well, these people are sick.
I don't want to be anywhere near these psychos.
They've gone insane, they've gone really insane.
I know, it's like, really, it's like, yes.
It's just like the people that believe,
oh, the episteme must be real,
because yeah, of course,
they're taking hundreds of 14-year-old girls
from like eighth and ninth grade
and flying them to an island off of Florida.
And nobody knew about it for months and months and months.
Right?
Does that make any sense?
Does that make any fucking sense at all?
It just doesn't make any sense to me.
But I see things as obvious to me,
because I'm kind of logical.
But it's like, these people believe everything.
Oh my god, Jeffrey Epstein.
I mean, if people don't believe in that,
I kind of think they're dumb.
I'm sorry to say there's people that believe in leaving like the narrative of the mainstream media, which is basically just like programming machine from for the America
It's like this programming you understand. This is all written. Most of us probably written by AI
Probably I put I have a ton a lot more originality in my music and a lot more myself of my music
I mean the fucking news has and it's the same news everywhere. You know, they let us read the same news everywhere. It's programming
It's like to program the society. It's called social engineering. They're looking at Tabastock Institute
It's really obvious to me, but then people understand if they haven't looked into it. Yeah, escape the matrix. I mean, it's like really
That's what the sheet
That's the thing where it comes to sheep and that's why they call actually they call the people like the people go him or they call them
cows like the low cows and they call them sheep
It's because they believe, they just are this high of mind.
They just believe everything they hear.
And it's like, you can't even talk logically to them,
or, and sometimes they'll make it really obvious
that it's fake, but I'll see it.
But it's like, sometimes they'll say,
if you have the eyes to see, if you have the ears to hear,
and some of these people are just blind and deaf,
and that's sad.
And I would love to like, you know, help them wake up,
but it's like, you really can't,
it's like they're too, most of these people
are just too foregone.
Like they're just they're just they're done like they're their brains and turn to
It's kind of like neon
goo
By now like really I mean it's sad it's sad
Basically people are asleep there is it in and out and we think oh
Well, we think that or most people think that the entertainment industry is like, oh, that's there to entertain us
Is there any wonder that they were entertain and
Train are very similar words and train and entertain. Okay, what is in train? It's like to lead the mind
It's like to it's like basically they can lead the minds anywhere. They want to for these social reasons, right?
And so we're like, why would they do that? That is a lot of work. Oh, I don't figure out. No, most people are really stupid
Hey, Norman, I can't even grasp the concept of being a functioning adult. I should
Norman Bates you
Dressed like your mother and so you're out of here. I don't I don't allow
Men that dressed like old dead women in my chest. So I'm sorry psycho
anyway
Yeah, well people didn't have a regular job, right?
You gotta just go to work and do the answers like working nine to five and work your whole life and then die, right?
That's how everyone has to do
Don't make your dreams come true. Don't do what you want. Do what you're just a whole to do
Do what you're supposed to do. Do what the society tells you to do. Do what's normal, right?
Right, I mean
That's what he's saying. It's like oh, well, I mean they think that who is he?
Fucking fucking psycho his name is Norman base. He literally all these people. They have these names of these satanic fucking evil
It's basically serial killing
Characters for movies. That's what they that's who they call that's what they vibe with that is their character. They've chosen for this show
I literally psycho a little Countess Bathory's a there's a vampire bitch that would kill young women and it's like and then she's telling us what to do. Oh
Lady Bathory exposed it
Samman, you're a fucking, you know why people love Samman because he's retarded and people
love to feel smarter than people, and so he's, everyone just feels smarter than them, so they
feel comfortable. That's why, that's the only reason I can think of that why he's popular
is because he's so stupid. I mean, it's like, maybe I should be stupid and then people would
like me too, but I just can't because I'm not. I can't even pretend to be stupid. I try it a
I can't I can't pull it off because then I say something smart and then people were like what's going on here
I don't like this guy anymore. Let's get him out of the community, you know
Community you love surprises. Oh, you have a suspense. Oh me too Calabasas. What was suspense? Yeah
Well, the suspense is I'm gonna ride you like a rapt just a moment and we're gonna marry
Sorry, I ruined the suspense. I'm so sorry.
One time I got kicked out of a chat because or I got hidden in his chat
Because I said something about Ilion Gonzalez like you have you heard of Ilion Gonzalez?
He's like it was like in like 1999 when I was in college and he came from Cuba on like a raft
And, like, he got found, and they wanted to report him and stuff.
I think I said the name Ilian Gonzalez in a chat,
and I think Christine and Samman were like,
oh, he's Doc Singh!
He's Doc Singh! Oh, my God, he's saying a name!
I'm like, okay, they don't...
And I couldn't even explain, oh, it's not anybody's name.
It's, like, Ilian Gonzalez, this, like, kid from, like,
25 years ago and from the news.
And they thought I was Doc Singh.
I wasn't... They think it's, like, Samman's real name.
It's not Ilian Gonzalez.
I know his last name, but I know all I'll say is that his name is Samuel, which he's already said, and he's a Taurus.
Oh, but he's Leo.
Okay, New York men think they are like a Tupac character, right?
They think that, yeah.
I'm more like Tupac than he is.
Tupac was gay.
Tupac, like the real Tupac is like, hello, hey, what's up?
He was like, I've seen him in an interview.
He's like, hi, and he's like this actor.
And he's like, hey, well, you know, he does this like, this, this rap and he looks kind of like it. No, he was a gaze can be. He was like in theater and stuff.
And he might be alive still for all we know. Like really, they mostly people just fake their deaths and like get a little plastic surgery or something or go to like some kind of like, you know, less populated place to retire because they get want to get away from these crazy Americans.
Americans are insane. He was beautiful. He was beautiful, but he was very gay. He was.
He was you ever see him in the bathtub and stuff like that. He does like bath naked bathtub flu shoot. So he was beautiful
but
Yeah, the thing is that when you sit on record when you sign your a record contract
It's not your music anymore. Like you it's basically like Ursula, right? So you sign your voice over
to a company that makes you sit, they use your voice and you, like whoever you are, to put out their message, right?
Fake Anxer, he was a ballerina, yeah exactly, you know, so yeah, he knows, it's like, I figure this out.
If you go and people just dig a little bit they can't figure this out
But it's like they won't they don't even like he didn't believe it like because they're just like oh my god
Oh me they're just like so programmed like the whole even the whole gangster stuff. It's all that's basically
Most of it was created in like in like the late 80s by like these white
Billionaires that are basically they own private prisons and they're like we need to we need to get some business going in these prisons
Let's start. Let's get all these let's get a lot of these inner city people
committing crimes and just arrest them all and
We'll charge the government like a hundred dollars per meal
For them their little little crappy meals are like a hundred dollars each
You know that's like it's like it costs like a thousand dollars a day to house somebody in prison
It's like that's like a luxury hotel and all this shit. That's how much the you know these private corporations are benefiting from these people
So of course they're gonna want to arrest everybody, right?
So sick. Yeah, you can look into this too. This is all documented
There's people that you know have been to these meetings
That's why do you think do you think that these gangster rappers are letting their kids listen to their music?
think about that or
Get anywhere near any of these any of this industry. No, no, no, they put them in the nicest
It's expensive private schools with all of
You know away from away from all of that. It doesn't even exist
And so they kind of go soft, but it's like, jeez, it's kind of dangerous.
And then they have to like, you know, basically, they put on this clown outfit.
That's all these rappers are clowns.
That's why they have like the sideshow bob hair.
They all have sideshow bob hair, and they talk, they mumble, you can't even
understand what they're saying, because it doesn't really matter anymore.
And the same man loves the music.
It's just terrible junk.
I know. No, no, I'm not saying, I'm not saying, I'm not saying, oh yeah, I'm just saying he was gay, but I'm not, it's not like there's anything wrong with me. I'm gay.
But yeah, he was a talented rapper too, but he didn't really like live this thug life. I mean, it's like, you can tell, I think, you know, he was kind of like more privileged of bringing a little bit.
But anyway.
That's neither here nor there. It's just like yeah, it's the same thing with like, you know, all these world leaders
We think oh the oh Kim Jong-un Kim Jong-un is like Korean. Well, he's actually, you know, I
Think he was born in like Switzerland or something like that
You know
And it's like and they went to these very fancy schools and it's like and then they all they're all groomed for these positions, right?
He had a sex. Yeah, that's that's sexy shiny head thing is like kind of like the white Tupac of the chat
Can you rap thing that is I would like to hear things that is rap sometime. So
And sure it's better than betas
Yeah, and bronze birds rapping. That's that's that's what people really sound like when they rap
They sound like beat and bronze but then you get all these like professional recording studios involved and it makes it sound a lot better. I
Mean, but it's like basically
You can't even remember the words anymore. So just a school darn mumble
It'll sound like this retarded person with Sam-Man on the internet.
Everyone loves them.
They'll sell a million copies.
That's all anyone who wants to buy is indecipherable garbage.
I mean, it's like, I don't know.
He's so...
I mean, Sam-Man is like a woman.
Like, really.
hysterical like kind of I mean not saying women are hysterical but it's just
like he acts like a woman I mean I say oh my god it's like it's like I was
almost embarrassed like oh my god the people know that he's like this like a
gay woman or like a gay man like woman kind of character that it's like kind of
like
And there's a reason he's on a camera.
He uses this picture, he looks like,
he looks like, you know, Emanuel Lewis.
He looks like some dwarf in the picture
or Beal's use or something like that.
It looks like a dwarf in this picture,
but I think that he just had an AI
that made him look kind of normal in it.
No, I think it looks like,
if any of you saw it, you would scream.
No, just like, I think Bita uses her like
fucking high school photo for her profile pictures and shit.
I mean, it's like,
They're just like oh, yeah, I mean jeez. I think she's like something like supermodel
With screen if you saw her
It's why she doesn't go on camera
Seeing him gay people wears McQueen. I don't know to find him
President. Oh, oh your president Kate. Oh, yeah, everyone. I know. Oh, well president Kate
What are you are the head of the community Kate the head of the community? I
Thought you were telling people not to come here
Oh my God, you are!
But anybody who tells not to come here, the doesn't.
Thank you, you're just, you do me a favor.
You're weeding out the herd.
I don't need a bunch of sheep here.
I need goats, I need independent goat-thinkers, not.
Oh, you know who, oh, you know she owns?
She owns you actually, and I'm gonna leave you here
because she'll be very mad when she sees,
oh, look it, no, you have a different name,
so you can't see who you are.
I think you're probably a key man or something.
Oh, yeah, I told you I tell you
You were told not to go here today also. Mm-hmm
Well, maybe they're a little bit jealous
Maybe that's the whole reason for all this outrage because it's like there's a little bit jealous and they don't like
Then I you know, I know too much but they're fucking pathetic ass lives, and they think I'm pathetic, please
Please
You can see these people I'm on camera guys
I'm if I'm pathetic you can see every little little bit of pathetic part of me if they're pathetic
Well, they can just hide behind the camera and criticize someone else get your attention off
It's like a magician doing a trick but because it's up that they're more like, you know David David copper top
Care David carrot top or something like that. I don't know they're not they're not David Copperfield. They're just like fucking
some gingers with the
Fucking that's further voice a little bit and everyone follows it. It's like really sad. It's really sad
But I will tell you the truth and people get scared as one that knows the truth
They're scared of me. They are they're like, oh my god
He's like and he's making money like I because I do make money too. I do good donations
I mean and it's like maybe it's not just from like like every
Everybody but it's like, you know people are very some people are very generous and I've been very very blessed and stuff
I think that and oh my gosh, dude. They try to destroy that shit ain't no party like a thing that is party
Hey, what's up ghostie ain't no party like a thing that is party, right?
Thing that is it's gonna be a thing that is it needs to you know
Get up you put a party hat on I
Want to hire thing that is a party clown. I'm gonna name him Pogo and
I'll basically be the John Wayne Gacy of the chat because I'm I think I'm retiring my serial killer
Your sound
I'm being too loud maybe it's ghosty what's up ghost
Ghosts, what are you doing? Ghosts are even in trouble. Kate and and beta and Sam man and trip trip and zip will give you a spanking for being here
Oh my god thing that is too. My god, you guys are not allowed to be here
Do you know they have their spies everywhere and what are they gonna do Barry said?
He's afraid he's gonna get killed if he comes here
He literally told me that I can show you the message
Where he says he said Kate said she would kill me if I go over there. I even asked him to come over
I just asked him as he said, like he said,
oh, he just wrote me more randomly.
He said, oh, I'm sorry, I would be in your chat,
but Kate said I'm not allowed to go there anymore.
And I said, really?
And then he's like, yeah, she said she would kill me.
And I was like, well, I'm not afraid of her.
I actually like Shrek.
And then all of a sudden the Shrek meme is made where she looks like frickin, you know
Doesn't look like Shrek or Fiona. She looks like like some some like, you know
The woman from Tangled with green skin and then it's like something like donkey. That's like like melting with my face on it
Okay, yeah, I see what you're doing there, please.
Yeah, one rolled up leaf, yeah.
So, I mean, it's like, I'm not even insulted.
Guys, I've had the worst,
I've got to call the worst things.
I've done nothing worse than getting me called.
I've done everything.
They've thrown everything at me except the kitchen sink.
Well, no, including the kitchen sink,
but you know what I did?
I refurbished my kitchen.
Now I have all new things.
Brand new kitchen sink, new refrigerator, air fryer.
I just, you know, I turn lemons to lemonade.
I'll put the link up for you.
He smokes the tobacco in Swisher
instead of putting weed in it.
Yeah, because it's cheaper.
You know how much, well, you know,
cigarettes are expensive.
Why is it so funny?
It's like that I spend $2 a day
instead of $12 or $15 a day.
Yeah, it's called saving money.
Here's a dog outside.
Oh, you're not muscular or intimidating ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb-ribb
I mean, you're not a good troll,
but you're kind of like qualify it long enough.
Remember when you send me that $2 and you're like,
oh, go buy yourself nail clippers.
Well, first of all, you know,
I'm not gonna buy nail clippers with it.
Second of all, you're just being rude and saying,
I'm dirty and so that's the troll thing.
And yeah, you turn into one,
you've just been spending so much time
and so much time on the beta and say,
and you know, and I, and people on your panel,
I mean, it's like, wow.
I mean, it reminds me of like me a little bit last year,
Oh, we have a guest. Let's welcome our guest. I mean, just make sure it's the correct person and one second
I don't like I can't even put up the fucking things anymore. Okay. It's gracious once again
Hello, sexy too sexy for my
Too sexy for my shirt too sexy for my pants too sexy
What's going on beautiful
I am beautiful. Thank you. Hey, hey, hey ghost. I thought he's talking I thought he's talking to me. No
No, I well I would I say it goes as handsome, but
you know
Anyway, how are you guys? How's your night? Okay, but man
I was waiting for you to hit the pen throw the panel down man so we could hit it up enjoying man
Fucking
We were on a panel earlier and we couldn't even talk because everyone was just screaming there was two people screaming the whole fucking
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I'll pay to see him naked. I don't give a fuck all that I did not say all that but
I mean, it's like yeah, he likes winning where the speedos and he finds it a dragon
And I was saying something about like he he really likes it. He likes the American flag one. That's what you've seen
Yeah, that's all that's all ones. I have I feel bad for ma'am
Yeah, because I think speedos the reason I've got them or I requested an easy bought them was because I thought it'd be kind of
Funny and like people would just like lavish. It's like I'm not dude
Yeah, I had some guy wears anything and fucking looks good in it no matter how he puts it
he's not you know America first
We're fucking hot something that Tyler wishes he could be I like it. Do you have a pair of speedo as is male?
Like he does he showed he showed me that or not is private private chat
I'm writing my boyfriend ghosts. Oh
Was your boyfriend
They're not they're not American flag. He's more Israeli
he's israel you have an israel speedo yeah yep yeah well even the even the name even the word speedo
is fun for me to say it's just fun i mean it's like it's funny and it's like and i took a shower
in them and saman watched it and now he has pictures of berries private parts spucking him
yeah
And I agree with that and very distressed. I understand why Kate doesn't like say man because he's you know
He's trying to take Barry away from her, but I think that is I see him in the chat
Yeah, I don't know a thing that is are you gonna come up here and
And I go
I'm glad we're having more open panels, and we invite Amish up here. It's really awesome
Look at his face Amish. My name is Ishmael. Have you heard of it? There's something like my name is Ishmael or something like that
The first word in like a Charles Dickens book or something. Does anybody know has anybody heard that? He said maybe later. Okay. Oh
Okay, I can look it up. Is that your real name or is it?
Okay. Oh, yeah, I know it's like there's another book and it says my name
I'm not my real name, but you know, just cuz you asked, you know, I'm saying I keep the rule with you
Yeah, just you know, you should lie on nobody. Nobody. No, buddy. My name is my real name is Casper
Yeah, nobody ever asked so why would I say anything you know can I get you're such a security number if you don't mind
It's a no call me ish mail is actually from Moby dip nobody got that
Call me ish. No iconic opening line from Herman Mell. Come on guys
It's a call no ish mail
All me ish man. No, I've never seen him, but I'm gonna check it out. It's a Moby Dick movie
He does like
I'm big so I don't know where Halo is. You know it makes sense. You know
Why didn't she say something that is
My little Amish
I like the office because they don't have
There's no almost people here because they don't have TVs or computers and so they're kind of like they're kind of like Hispanics, but
They can feel cheap and quicker
They're like craftspeople in like Canada that like make really expensive. Hmm. You need a shed belt, you know, call up some Amish
I mean, I need some Amish stuff. I'm a fishman
I'm an Amish
Amish, he's he said he's
He's gonna keep denying that shit. It's been like a week now. We know you're fucking honest. I'm playing like a week
First black Amish I've ever met but I've met him
Are you doing my show because or like where'd you
He's been on a lot of shows good. I mean, it's like I'm not like
I'm not the community. I'm my own
Well, he found you because of the speedo content. He really liked that. Yeah. Yeah, I mean, I didn't see it
I didn't see it. I heard that they were trolling
You were trolling Tyler on another panel, and you know, I was hearing it. I was over here
You gave me details. Yeah, they were trolling ghosts and ghosts like fuck it. I don't care
I'm on psychs fucking page and you know, I support him to look at him on his Speedos and I would pay to watch him naked
Well, Ghost, can you please pay me because I think you haven't even donated like a-
I don't know how much you want!
You see you send me another thousand dollars, please. I need I need to I need to live
Can be an ishmael I'll go for partner ish no go 500. Okay. Okay. Well
Seems fair. Maybe should be I did it is yeah, I did unblock chibi chibi
Okay, yeah, I think we I think but I think we're good
But it's like the thing is even the people even the person that everyone's like screaming about it's not like he's like you really
Even in here, I mean as I or I mean as I think he's he was fine, but it's like fine in here
It's always just like a big like
It's like a big like non-issue anyway. It's like I'm not gonna like micro manage
Oh my god, look at everyone's coming on record. He's coming to chat and oh my god
And it's like then I watched everyone's like screaming. Oh my god. They're the most evil videos
He's like sitting in front of like a computer screen talking to people. It's like so stupid. It's like he's like a gamer
It's like but it's like so Sam is there to see that play with him playing
Roblox and UGO with you know kids all day don't care
He's fucking friends with doxers and and these criminals and I mean most of the stuff that Alexander mares
Really true, but it's like
Sounds like it's most friends
well
Let's not get anyone in trouble. This one talks. He's criminal criminal genius. I'm gonna dox them right now
OK, you know he's not going to doxy, don't worry.
Well, you want somebody to see it along the way?
I have a question though.
Where'd that cat go?
Yeah?
Where?
What guy?
The cat.
Oh, the cat.
I'm talking about the tux, the boy cat?
No.
I'm talking about the smaller one.
And the one that came in last night?
I'm also, am I breathing heavy in the mic?
I'm not.
Yeah, you sound you sound like your 500 pounds goes. Are you okay? I am fat. I'm also coped the fuck out. I'll be honest with you
You're pimped the fuck out
Yeah
Cane and a purple jacket
And a hat I came up here to talk to my good friend ish mouth, okay
Is the issue or is it a no, we don't know we're gonna figure it out tonight
Is it's my ill is my is my ill? Oh
It's electric ill
By the way that panel earlier
And I got as money for 20 does he want to come up here? I see him in the chat. By the way
Of course he wants to go crazy, dog. He's gonna come up here. Of course. It was literally two hours of just yelling
It was was it were they yelling about
I don't fucking know
Who knows?
When I turned on this show, I'm like, oh my god,
I hear that Harry Tzatzika.
Oh, that's a nice flannel, brother.
You got on?
A bunch of times.
I mean, I'd look at it once in a while.
I mean, I was like, I listened to Beatus.
Beatus was just a big bitch fest about me.
She's like, I guess the whole point of the panel,
the whole theme of the six hours or whatever she was on
was, I don't think I'm gonna have him on.
I don't, I want you.
I don't think I'm gonna have that psyche anymore.
But she doesn't think, but she will.
I mean, she's like,
she's like, cause he's almost as bad
as like the, as all these people now.
Oh really?
I mean, it's like they're not even bad, but it's like
Like you don't want
Dogs man, of course he wants you. What do you mean? He doesn't want you
How dare you?
How dare you say that
Very disrespectful. Come on, of course he does. I don't want you as a mod
the
Making I'm making it like he's late to the lol. We're going Dutch tonight. Yeah, did I do what? Yeah? I'll do it right now
I'll do it right now Danny before it happens
Now it smells let me ask you a question about your backstory. How are you black and Amish?
Who says who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black and who said I'm black
I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I miss. No, no, no.
How long does it take you to build a barn? If you don't mind build a barn. I don't know. I never built it before
Yeah, dad. Well, never mind
No, that's not my
I don't do those
I'm gonna build her, you know, you know, psych, you know, I had my back on a podcast before. Do you know that?
many times many times he came up and descended me i will always defend you bro well yeah i know it's
like sometimes this community can change people into like you know evil people but like you know
I don't give a fuck if I would you know what it is. I got tired of everybody. Just like
He's a fucking human being well, you can't just always step on somebody and punch them like a punching bag and
Feel them like shit. There's got to be somebody else, bro
Well, they kept they kept asking for a troll. They kept saying
I gave them one
Yeah
I think psyche understands it a little bit, you know, oh my god, I got a question ask like
You got here you got deck on hand. Yeah, can I give one card?
Yeah, that's on you. That's on you. I'm not into that. I'm not into that you guys do what you got to do
Please don't involve me
Like a Leo, but it's a kind of like like a Leo, maybe
We're definitely
Come back
Esma shut up you're getting a reading
Two to ten cards bro. Come on one card is not enough
I'll give him the bitch card either. Be respectful.
I'll just give you three for Ghosts.
You've got to do ten cards, bro. Come on, Tyler.
Do you want to give me three?
Well, yeah, but, okay.
So, and Ghosts also, like, coming out of your hermit mode,
because this is, like, a hermit-
Hmm.
...versus, so kind of, like...
You've been wanting to like not be alone like to like because you do spend a lot of time alone
I think but when you're comfortable alone
But it's like this is like also good to like get out a little bit and to be with mm-hmm, and the socializing
That's why I'm going YouTube channels exactly exactly
I got the seven of wands and so something really fast. Oh seven of wands
fast-moving communication, fast-moving energy of a like something happening in your family.
You're gonna hear some, you're gonna hear about something probably tomorrow or in the
in the near future or some kind of news is gonna come, something's gonna come really fast for you
and it might, might be even like, you know, just like, uh, that's having to do with that hermit,
the coming out of your hermit mode. It might be whippin which ishmo, ishmo's asked,
but can you give him a card reading if you don't mind? No, he said no, he said no, but
if he says yes, I'll pull him one. No, he did not say no, he was joking, he wants one card. Okay,
cash for one card for you
oh you got the sun
and that's the most positive
you got the car
you got the sun car which is like
it's just very very good energy
it's like you know it's a warm
voodoo
see it has this little boy right there
labyrinth deck and so the sun looks kind of
evil
just like see the sun
I mean
Innocence they get this like kind of like carefree kind like happy you're like a happy person
Maybe a little bit dumb. We don't know we're sicker it out
Man no, nobody's dumb anymore, right? It's like that except for him. No, it's like, I mean he's like she's called
Did you just say scam man? Yeah scam man is
I'm Kabbalah
Donation I'll read you. I'll read you Pokemon card. Okay. I'll poke a you're the god of war. It looks like
The god of the sun
what happened to my channel since you were gone
I don't know like what do you think it's like what do you think it's bad better or worse
There's not a lot of people here today because Kate has said nobody can nobody's allowed to come here
I don't mean son as in son. I mean son is like I'm your daddy. Yeah
Well, yeah, I think it's working, but it's like I'm so thankful. Thank you Kate
Cuz I didn't want those people that are in your chat over here, and they just bother me
And be dead to the same thing I don't I don't I don't want those people over here
Yeah, I'm not from 420s a channel either. Well, yeah, I mean everyone's allowed to you are
You were over there. No, I was over there. Yeah, I hang out there. I hang out everywhere. You kidding me, but I'm not from that channel
Take it off tomorrow like
good like old times take it off take it off
oh yeah you shut the fuck up
I mean now I don't instead of giving mods I just hide people for the night and then I let him back on the next day sometimes
I thought you were cooking or something
yeah well
no no I'm asking Tyler if he thought he was cooking
no what were you cooking what
I thought you was cooking
oh my god that was Sam and says I'm cooking what
I don't know you know when when you think you have something and you're like
I'm a trolling shit, and it doesn't work out for you
You know what's fucked up that you use psyche right to read a card and uses powers right and not fucking send a single
I have a ghost of readings for the rest of them not send a single dollar is fucked up
You know he sent me a lot of money. Oh, that was before but that's before
$0 he will he will be sending me some money soon. You always sends I know that that's what I was
We're in those Speedos and he had died there
I don't think says women when you give me mod of 10 times removed it 10 times in banding 20 times
Yes, I remember that and I'll do it again
Do it again like I well, I know I can't I kind of tend to just like forgive
I'm so like I just want to say that ishmael did must be me
He said that your hair looks really nice and that you're wearing a really nice shirt. Oh, thank you
I thought that was nice if I'm here to see you. Are you a good-looking man?
Blasian
I'm not I'm not I'm not good-looking. I'm handsome. Oh, you're handsome. You're not like ghost who has a face for radio
Yeah, he's a tub of water with like a fucking long beard
Good in in fucking overalls. Yeah, I got a face. I got a face right here. Like that's fucked up
For West Virginia, he looks like a red pit of West Virginia before West Virginia
That's like not even a compliment. That's a backhanded compliment for West Virginia
Well, that's Virginia. That's good
You look like a troll, but you know, I'm sexy and you know, it's not playing with me
for you, damn
Good as fuck
Yeah, for you for California. You're a to a strong too. I'm like that. I'm like a
For an Amish is smell looks like a like a three
I'm like a nine everywhere else in California.
I'm like a six or seven.
You ain't no fucking nine in the rest of the country.
California is really like fucking extra.
The hottest people in the world come to California.
It's like 10.
No, maybe a four.
I'll give him a four.
Four being on this, you know, I'm on a four.
But neither of you guys have any pick.
Look, it says it.
It says it, it.
IT.
I'm surrounded by it.
Yeah, put us beside each other actually.
I'm gonna get TI.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
You're very sexy, you're very sexy.
Like, you know, in West Virginia at Kabbalah,
too strong, you would be a-
Nah, you know, like a little like,
sometimes we're mutated up there, you know?
Sometimes, you know, you get like a second or third.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm just saying, I might be mutated a little bit, yeah?
He's exactly as he is, yeah.
I think he has like a voice changer or something the fuck was that so it's
Robert it's what sexy Rob sounds like when you get to the panel and he went
back he's like Alex McQueen I window I would have sex with you and I said back
stage and I did like I said you could be a WWE wrestler but you don't do
steroids yeah you could be like one of those midget wrestlers yeah you know
those little like those little midget damn
Yeah, that's what you'd be it'd be like the little one
Ray Mysterio, yeah a cute one though. No
You could be a cute like garbage pale kid. He's kind of like he's like a balding like a cute garbage
No, no garbage, not cabbage patch
Basically, he looks a little bit like a half a photo of the munchkin
It looks like he looks like one of the lollipop guild basically
of the
we represent
No, he's very good. He's very good. No ghost is good. He's a nice oompa-loompa
I'll put on a little bronzer
I'm more of like the wizard or maybe todo. I don't know. You want to be dr. Oz brother? You can't be dog. Oh
Dr. Oz is from Oprah. He was like
The real the real wizard of Oz was like a con man and he wasn't even like a real wizard. He just ended up
You know, we got so you're conning us then
No, but
I'm
Got him hoodwinking hoodwink. I'm doing more of a hoodwink on you
Oh
the
Triple H with anorexia. Triple H, I can be triple X, triple H that looks like anorexia as WWE wrestler. What language is that? You're not even going to get a grammar.
Psyche can be triple H that looks anorexia as a WWE wrestler. Okay. I don't know. I don't know what that means. I'm sorry.
Um, I look like I look like triple H if you went to like a concentration camp like this. Nope. No fuck. All right
No, but I'm sorry. That's all fucked up
No, I mean, it's like I really I really could be I mean, but uh, I want to know I want to gain 60 pounds
I'm actually
Trying to batten myself up right now
Give me 60 pounds heavier. How would I look at 200 pounds? How would I look ghost six three two hundred pounds?
How was that?
I wouldn't know if you've got a six foot three. So I'd be like norm. I'd be like I'd be like fine
No, I would look good
Can't believe we made the Amish guy leave I didn't make anybody leave first of all people their own free will here
I just can't I can't like start the no trapping people here or else. I'll get it. I'll get arrested and people will say
Oh my god, he's
False imprisonment. Yeah
I'm not in prison anybody here
Obviously not many people everyone's afraid of Kate. I mean, yes, she does look like she could eat people, but I don't think she really would
No, she liked it. What does she like to eat? Yeah, I think probably it looks like a cannibal to me. Can I eat dick?
Probably
What fuck?
No, but not like not suck on it like she wants to eat it like she wants to eat it
Life in a fork
Shit
Are you interested in that?
You're kinky. I like a little vampire. I like a little zombie. I like a little you know, like a little bit of that slasher shit, yeah
But those aren't real things those are just like, you know, Hollywood
I've known a sucky best once in my life
I've known several of them. I've actually know several of them and I've known some vampires
I've done some aliens. I've known some trolls and I've known some dum-dums
Well, I've got a couple of dum-dums and I'm talking to one right now
Get back. I'm so sorry
You don't use my word sir. He's joining here. Hey, Johnny
Johnny Cowboys she's here earlier
Sorry, I missed her home. I'm so sorry. I mean, I mean to miss anybody. I don't see her
Is she a long time ago?
Yeah, it was a while ago. Well, she was typing. It was a while here. I'm sorry. I missed you. Um, yeah
I'm sorry
Yeah, I psyche I got timed out triggered joke joke ghost is the leader of the dump
The lollipop guild here in the dumb dumb guild
Represent the dumb
Who the fuck is Chanel or is that was that the name Chanel? Yeah, she's you know, she's a fashion designer
She a dumb dumb
No, she's not dumb. She's a leader of Dumb Dumbs maybe. We don't know. We're gonna figure it out. I thought you were
Hey, Joanie
Is she there? Is that Joanie there? Hi, Joanie. Hi, Joanie. Yeah, okay. I'm actually
Trying to make an app right now. It's like a really cool app that will actually do a lot of cool stuff. Uh-oh
It's like but it's not working right now, but I was like it's actually gonna be able to be like help me do some stuff
By the way, I'm just gonna point out that it's not it's crashing out earlier
And he left so quick tonight. It's fucking funny, but he was crashing out earlier. He was
Did you have permission to crash out?
He did not have permission. He didn't ask permission either.
That's fucked up, yeah.
You get permission from GOES before you do that next time.
Yeah, he had to ask permission, brother.
And you gotta, if you're gonna crash out at least,
make it a good crash out.
Yep.
Well, let me see.
I don't see anybody here. I seem to 420 earlier. I see an instrument
I've seen a couple other people they want to come up here and like fucking troll the
Not that I'm up here. They run. It's like what you wouldn't all they can lying out
There's 22. Like did you say like twice as many people here? Like I really do think people but I'm happy that there's like half as many because
Those were just people that I didn't like any of the trolls
Well, not even good trolls though. That's the thing if you're a good troll here
That could be that could almost I could almost make an argument that might be a good thing
I can never make the argument like a troll is ever okay, but if you're a good troll
You know, maybe to help out the content, you know, there's so many people that come here that I've known for a long time
And then I'll be like and I'll be happy that we'll be my mods and everything and then they'll be in another chat
Like just like kissing someone's butt and then they'll be like
But here's thing his nest is different than if they're like talking shit though
Yeah
I mean, they are, I was literally looking at the chat and reading terrible things about
me.
And I'm not even, I mean, and it's like, and they're like, oh, well, you know, we make
sure you ice psyche out and like, nobody go over there, nobody donate, nobody support
them, nobody, nobody, don't even go there to hang out, don't even, don't even go to
their hang out.
If you, if you go over there, you better be giving them a hard time.
That's what she said.
And so, and they know they're not going to be able to get away with that now because I'm like fucking my finger
And then imagine if we would have said that same shit about her we
It's like Jesus. I mean, it's like I I think I just might maybe mention that I was like
Oh my god
She should worry about her own kids and then my the my chat, but then it's like then she's like now
I'm talking about her kids and stuff and it's like I'm meeting people are saying. Oh my god
Yeah, like now I'm being called like horrible names or like I'm doing anything. It's like so I mean, you know, okay
he's like I gave psyche a second chance and I shouldn't have blah blah blah blah well it's like
you know what I didn't ask for a second chance you started coming over here on your own you were
like you know I know you said that you donated five dollars in a year or something like that
I mean, jeez, I mean, it's like I was like nice enough to let you on the panel and like, you know
Like try to promote your show as much as I could and I didn't do anything to you
All I did was like try to run my own show and not listen to you when you told me what to do and it's yeah
Yeah, I mean, it's like and everybody else gets like oh a few days of grace and to like like research some of these things
I even know this person's like all this stuff they were saying about this guy
But I just didn't want to take it is and all these people that are just trolls of mine telling what to do
No, I'm not gonna do it. I'm not gonna do what they want to and especially maybe I'll
I mean it's like I do believe in things like forgiveness. I do believe in redemption
I do believe in like people can change really better
I I believe in all these things and so be going against everything. I really believe in
I always let Pete anybody who wants to come up here come here always can I push back a little bit
If you don't mind
I don't think that's always a good idea if you're always forgetful like if you're always forgetful
Like if you forgive somebody and you learn back on your channel, they'll probably, I mean,
well, like, sometimes they're telling me,
I mean, what, yeah, here's the one thing, if you like,
But I'm, but I'm a Christian though, son.
And here's the way.
I let somebody up here and then they wait and they track you down and they killed you then I feel bad and I wouldn't let them
But here's my thing. I think you can be judgmental as a I'm a Christian
I can be judgmental and I don't believe like don't believe in that born again verdant shadow believe it like yeah
God can forgive you, but
Christian then if you're like going against the teachings of Jesus well no well God can forgive you doesn't mean I have to
Well, how about Jesus?
Yeah, Jesus can forgive you. I mean, I have to what did Jesus say did he say to become God or do you say be like God?
He also said go forth and send no more and a lot of these horrors that get saved they go forth and send more
The human beings are just we're just simple by nature even like
I'm just saying now. I don't need I don't know why everybody's like eight-month Christmas is like we don't have to like
Judge as a Christian. No because a lot of them are hypocrites because they did not Protestant brother. I'm not Protestant
those
It means
Yeah, like every so often you throw cards out of a deck and it's one to three cards
That's not orthodox Christian. That sounds more like the world like what I am which is an occultist. Oh
Yeah
What is tarot me?
Tarot comes from the word Torah
Which is like the the first Bible the Bible
It's the the Hebrews, you know, and that's where the word tarot comes from the Torah
There's even a the high priestess. There's a lot of Hebrew Hebrew symbolism in them
Is that where they like like nine year olds
Excuse me
The Torah
Torah the first five books of the bible. I think it's genesis genesis exodus leviticus numbers and deuteronomy
All right
Yeah, I think that's the Torah not anything to do with nine-year-olds. That's I think are you think is long and I was I was I fucked up
Even Islam too is like that thing too is like sometimes they would arrange marriages when the when the when they're
the people were children still, and then they would marry when they would get older, but they would arrange for marriage.
Uh, yes, it's debatable. It depends when you want to, like, when they are children, and it depends, like...
I've never talked about actual sex. It said, like, you know, there could have been a wife, but I don't think that was, that was inflicted necessarily in the scene.
I mean, it's...
I think she was dying.
You think she was dying?
I just got on debate about some. Pretty sure she was dying. I don't remember, but...
Lying or dying?
nine like nine years I
know I'm saying that they would arrange marriages sometimes when people were children and then they would yeah
They were an adult, but they would they would like basically
Married like when they became an adult, right?
So they arranged that shit and they couldn't communicate until they were adult. I believe so
I think that's I don't know. We have to look it up. I just got a debate about this
I'm pretty sure that's not how it was, but I'll take your word
There's also over a thousand years ago and there's like, you know
There's things like where people used to have a lifespan of like 30 years old and so it was like kind of different
Right. It was like they're kind of more in a rush than we are nowadays wherever looks like a hundred
So it's like I don't know it's like I'm not I'm not I'm not saying it's right or wrong. I'm just saying
that we don't know the law
and I also don't want to get into it
I just had a debate about it but I don't want to get into it with you
I'm just here hanging out
I know I'm in and of trouble ghost
now they're gonna say oh my god
I mean it's like
a lot of say is that
people have a lot of different beliefs and stuff like that
there's also these like
I mean
there's good things to believe in and bad things to believe in
I think that would be common sense
There's what good things to believe in bad things to believe in well
I mean basically beliefs are like beliefs are just things you like
Kind of like you can believe in a fairy tale you can
Well, yeah, but you have to get your morals from somewhere
So if you get your motion like a fairy tale could it be good? Yeah, it is with a moral code
Yeah, some some atheists are actually pretty good people believe they're not
Right and so it's like, yeah, so exactly so it's like doesn't necessarily you're never gonna
This is why we don't argue there speak we've argued before by the way
But this is why I asked you for a car because like I might be some type of way
But I can respect you and your beliefs and I can't appear and I asked for a car or something
Yeah, yeah
Just because I don't believe in that doesn't mean I can't respect you and what you believe in
You know why I mean, it's like I basically I don't even believe in things
I just have a fate or a knowing this actually and like just from like
Experiencing certain things and so I'm I don't question
It's like I just have been knowing this is like it's been proven to me some certain things and
But that's everybody has this
I've talked to you for like I know people's gonna talk chef talk to you for like three years now like
I've already made the argument three years ago. I don't believe in that shit and
I don't really feel like doing it tonight. Is that so good doing what?
I'll argue with you. We've argued like I've talked to you like three years ago, dude arguing around me debate. I'm just talking
Oh, no. Yeah, we're talking. Yeah, I agree with that. What I'm saying is I'm not gonna start a debate, you know
Unless you want to have one. I mean
And people hate that so much give him money. Oh
Uh, you go up there and talk to him, it's like, yeah, I go up, he's my friend, I talk to him.
Yeah, what do you do with your friends? You talk to them. What the fuck?
They don't want me they don't want they want me to be like irrelevant
They want me to be like shut they want me to be like some kind of like they want me to go away basically
Which I'm not gonna do because I'm part of that community like they can just go away for me and then that's it
I mean just like nobody has to go to anybody's channel. They don't want to
threatening people and and and being like, you know weirdos about it. They are being weirdos. I mean, it's like
I've never said anything like that like I only promoted these people I've never said don't go to anybody's so what they're doing is wrong
But there really is because especially I promoted them let them post their channels my chat share their show
I mean, it's like so much. I just helped them so much
And without even asking for anything in return and it's like and then for them to do this to me
It's like for no really no reason just because they just disagree with something like some kind of like no thing
Just as uh, it's kind of shocking, but I mean there's a little disrespectful. I think well, they suck
I mean it's just like they're just they're just they're stoutless
Pretty horrible people I would say and they're gonna they also have a meme game my karma
Well, let me look at their karma, and I really do hope they do and I hope it's bad
But I'm not I don't I really don't help the worst but you know
They're probably it probably just would be bad because they're putting negative energy in the world and they should lose all the
All the numbers that they're trying to get me to lose
But I'm happy that people are gone that are not here because I don't like Tom Cruise's little fella everywhere
He's like five foot eleven or four foot eleven. You're from Scientology. No, you're not
If you're in Scientology, you have to be careful because you're gonna cause
the
Hey, baby. Hey. Hey, go stay
The first thing that is we're gonna join I'm gonna I'm gonna go to some smoke, but I do must still be up here
But I might have to meet up for like a minute. I'm gonna play I'm gonna play a video while you're gone
And anybody can if they wanted to
Okay, oh, okay, so thank you. You like the Elvis of the Shats sure you are sure you are
You're like that you're like you're like the mini Elvis you're like the dwarf Elvis of the Chats
Are you calling me a dumb dumb Elvis you're calling? I'm saying to the guy in the chat
Okay, go see I'll see you in a little bit. Love you. Yeah, give me five. Is that cool?
Over here. I'll be here. I'll be right here
Maybe later. Yeah, he's doing stuff. Well
Okay, I'm gonna play a song
Here you go. This is my brand new hit. This is called
Was it called me a permission to crash out. No, it's not it's called. Yeah, it's called power
It's educational
You're invisible
Not weak
Just too available too eager
Given to people who don't respect you, but the world doesn't care about your heart
It cares about your value
And if you can't control perception
You'll spend your life being used
Replaced
People judge with their eyes not their hands they see results not your struggle
intention and honestly, they don't care about your sacrifice, about your purity, about your good heart, you want respect, demonstrate strength, you want loyalty, prove value, you want people to take you seriously, show them that losing you as consequences.
Curity
To emotional
To eager
But all of that can change starting now
I control my value
I'm irreplaceable undeniable
Control my value
Scarcity creates value availability destroys it gold is rare. That's why it matters air is everywhere
That's why it's worthless. The same rule applies to you
If you're always there always saying yes always dropping everything you become like air essential
Maybe taking for granted worthless in their eyes
Mackie a belly watch the most powerful the winter ones constantly in every one space they
Ability is killing you when you respond to everything immediately when you never say no
You're training people to disrespect you
You're teaching them your time means nothing
That you're desperate for their attention
And desperation repels power
Master strategic withdrawal
Don't answer every call immediately
Let some messages sit say no to requests that don't serve you
Create space between yourself and others
Something magical happens
People start wondering about you
Scarcity creates curiosity, curiosity creates desire, desire creates power
Stop pouring yourself into people who give nothing back
Stop being emotionally available to everyone
When you become scarce, not from arrogance, but self-respect
You force people to earn access to you, the ones who don't
Let them go, they were never adding value anyway
You teach people how to treat you by what you tolerate
If you tolerate disrespect, you get more
If you tolerate being taken for granted
They're chasing you
My time is currency, my presence is precious
My energy is mine, I control the axis
I control the narrative, I control what's given
I control my value, I control my value
Seven keys to power, not cruelty.
Strategy, not manipulation, awareness, they judge you by.
When you show not your heart, two value is the measure of worth not effort.
Three scars, city builds power. Availability destroys it for.
Competence over charisma always.
Five, control your emotions before they control you.
Six, walking away is your greatest leverage.
Seven, reputation is currency, guarded like gold
These aren't tricks, this is how power actually works
Machiavelli showed us 500 years ago
Most people ignored it, wanted to believe the world was fair
That kindness wins, that hard work is enough
But you're not most people, you're here because you want the truth
And the truth is this, the game is already being played
The only question is whether you're playing or when they're being played
I control my value, I am irreplaceable, I am undeniable, I am the one playing, not the one being played.
Fracture not the fall every scar speaks in a language that we can't recall
Betrayal wasn't chaos. It was coded design a map of where you trusted a map of every blind line
They smile like allies move like knives in the dark left you bleeding in silence
Just to study the mark, but you didn't disappear you translated the pain turn
Humiliation into data
No reaction for free every move calculated every silence a key you don't chase validation you withdraw your demand now
They reach for your presence. They don't understand
calculated state unpredictable rhythm impossible read you become the answer they secretly need you
don't reveal you imply you suggest let them build your power inside of their chest scarcity sharpens
the value you hold distance converts attention to gold
Design what you
And those that don't remember when your shadow moved before your feet
Whispered things you couldn't keep
The walls would breathe in slow and low
Every secret you don't show
Every version left behind
Still alive inside your mind
You said, am I the one who's dreaming?
I said, you never left at all
You are something else, wearing pieces of yourself
Faces hanging in the air
Try them on if you still care
Every mask of life you wore
Every life still wanting more
You said something's always watching
I said yes, but so I-
says you're
When I say it's over, lady, what for you?
I don't like it, leave.
Well, you're actually a time-dower right now, so.
Can't reply to me, but that's the rude.
Yeah, he's three foot tall.
Hi Alex, how are you?
Let me get my link up.
Who are these people?
Oh, we didn't just over.
It's like, how about go to your own show
and then you can run however you want.
You can play whatever you want on your show.
Don't ask me, sarcastically ask me when it's over, bitch, where that person is, I don't
want you here, if you're going to complain, annoying people, you're lucky to be here,
you're lucky to be graced by my talent.
You got guys know your value or else everyone's gonna just walk all over you
True you like you're worthless
Right know your value
You'd be back breakfast time. Okay. I'll see you later. Sexy you sexy Rob
Okay
Yeah, actually like sweet music, but everyone should start doing lies when he starts playing live, right? Oh
Why just the I'd love to I'd love that right? Oh
I just I didn't mean to do that. Hold on. I was an accident Alex. Oh my god, but I just do
I'm so sorry. I was an accident Alex
Queen I can fucking computers all slow now because it's like all this fucking software. I'm running to fucking run this thing
I was we're time over 300 seconds. I'm sorry
I'll fix it
Okay. Here we go. There we go. Okay. I'll fix it. Alex? Okay. Here we go. I'll fix it, Alex.
Fixed. Here you go. I'm going to pin my link.
Okay. I was like, who hit Alex? And I was like, oh, me. Oopsy. Oopsy. Okay. Okay. Now I'm going to
Word ghost go he's at five minutes. I know I think I think ghosts fell into the well. I think lassie is looking
It was an accident it was an accident
Come on back up
Thank you for the compliments though. I appreciate it. Here you go
You're back. I know that my computer was freezing. I was not cold, but it was you know
Yeah, if anyone of the mods it's like if I feel like someone needs to be untimed out
You just like time up for 10 seconds that it just acts actually it will
Let them back in 10 seconds
But I've gotten into like our arguments with the ghost
For typing out for 10 seconds, and he's like watch every 10 seconds like it was 10 seconds. It's like really
Short time and the 10 seconds is over long ago, but you know me and I don't know so
Okay, I'm trying to find
See the software I was using was free, but it was not very good. I mean it's not pretty good. Oh my gosh
I'm locked out of this account too
Okay, how are we doing?
Okay.
So, let's see, you're okay.
Yeah, I think that this is good.
I hope this is good.
How is everybody doing in the chat?
I'm trying to think.
I have some coffee, or I still have my hot coffee here.
Okay Joe, ghost will be back in 30 seconds.
I've just got softer since you've been gone, yeah.
Oh yeah, he said, oh yeah, I think, I think, I might have seen it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry Alex, how are you?
Chubby toes, ghost says chunky, it's chunky toes, ghost chunky.
I like the word chunky better than chubby
No, it's okay
Yeah, I thought like people are always like what do you like I am I am like actually studying to become certified in some of these
as I get a
As a professional so you know sky's the limit. Those are the where the jobs are to pretty good jobs available
And I'm I will have a nice portfolio of things by the time I'm by the time I get through it. So I'm actually pretty
Pretty optimistic about it. So
Even though these are things I'm wasting time. It's like actually it's not just like it's so easy to do. It's like actually
You know
There's a lot more to it than people just think.
I mean, yes, it's easy to use.
It's another thing, programming it,
which is what we're doing right now.
We're training it, programming it for the future.
And people will be thanking us in the future
because we're gonna make it so it doesn't like take over
and try and put us in camps and stuff like that.
Like, I ain't met people.
People are actually wanting that which is like a really scary thing. I mean it's
like the fact that nobody bashing bad in an eye when Kristen Marie was like oh
yeah well this person should be like you know disfigured murdered and I was like
well Crystal isn't that a kind of against like the United States like
Constitution where it's like no cruel and you punishment and stuff like that I
know that some things maybe do but I don't know she was seems like a little
bit of overreaction kind of kind of insane kind of scary actually
Which is why I'll be a little bit more more understanding and lenient towards people that just do stupid shit on the internet
You know, it's not like they're like hiring a hitman or something
Oh my god
People are just stupid kind of a sad. I'm like right belong in this world. It's really it's like I don't know if I can
Yeah, run a bunch of the same people well, I'm not you guys, but you know
Everybody else
Nuts, okay, let's see
Here goes to 30 seconds, I'll just play one more thing. I'll just wait around. I'm almost sitting up
At night, yeah, oh the Rudy's up there. What are you doing? Oh the are you talking about the birds? Oh the birds. Yeah
Rudy's looking over the banister, like Santa was like,
oh my God, his cats are staring at the wall,
that he's punishing his cats by making them look at the wall,
or they're going crazy, and he was like,
oh, there's probably just bugs all,
and cockroaches all over it and stuff.
Have you ever seen a cockroach?
I don't think I've ever seen a cockroach
go across my wall on the show.
I mean, it's like, jeez, what are we not now?
Oh, ghosts, but not now.
Only one though. I don't know. I'm missing the conversation.
Okay, well here. I'll be right back.
You are not dragging.
You are cargo.
Something else has hands on the wheel.
And it knows your name.
You're in your bloodstream, signing all your thoughts
Smiling in the mirror while you're real self-wrought
It's polite, little prisoner, trained to obey
You call it being good, but you're decaying that way
You swallow every instinct, fire your teeth down smooth
Call it self-control, but you just removed your proof, you had claws
You had fire, you had something divine
Now you apologize for crossing your own line
Call John Whisper from the grave
Make the dark conscious, so it digs your cave
But you muted the message, sanitize the pain
Weaponized Gloom
You built a mask so perfect even you forgot
Polished every angle till you're so got caught
They don't love you, they love the role you placed
And an ovation for a ghost in a display
Laugh on command, not on cue
Every yes you fake is a fracturing you
You feel that hollowness, that echoing space
Now pretending it's you, take back the throne, reclaim the room, turn your saddle from a cage
Into a weaponized boom
Everything you hate is a mirror
Every trigger gets clearer, arrogance, that's your buried ground
Laziness, that's burnout drown, jealousy maps where your hunger lives
Raid shows what your silence gives, your enemies are blueprints in disguise
them right, you weaponized.
and permission to exist as a man.
The moment you stop apologizing for a breath
is the moment your presence starts to fire in jail.
Talk to your moves like they're sitting across.
Negotiate storms instead of taking the loss.
That voice in your chest isn't random or fade.
It's a signal.
This isn't healing, this is integration.
You don't become good, you become whole, and once you're whole, reality starts bending
around.
Everybody gotta take names in the air like a trial. I didn't make by now pick a side prove
You're one of us funny how fast that support turns to pressure and disgust. I said, I don't know the story
I'm not signing up on claims you want instant verdicts. I don't play those games
Don't pay for then I'm asking for more that defense. That's me checking the floor
Like in the show, till I didn't follow where you wanted me to go
This is my platform, not your community
You don't get to vote on what I believe
You want control, dressed up as a unity
I see the strings, I don't agree
You draw your lines and expect me to trace it
Call it standards, I call it stage
Now it's noise trying to speak over me
But this is mine, not your...
He's yelling different names on the stage
Everyone knows ya, everyone says
But nobody stops to question the threads
Proof in the DMs I didn't review
Or proof you decided was already true
You want me to act on a crowd made case
Then punish me when I don't keep pace
Then a few people now I'm afraid
Or maybe I'm done with the games you play
Like in the show, till I didn't follow where you wanted me to go
This is my platform, not your community
You don't get to vote on what I believe
You won't control dressed up as a unity
I see the strings, I don't agree
You draw your lines and expect me to trace it
Calling standards, I call it stage
Now it's noise trying to speak over me
But this is mine, not your community
Now executioner live in my chat
Nah, I'm not Bill Light
To keep you agreeing with me
You drew your lines and I didn't chase it
You called in loss, I replaced it
Now it's me standing where I choose to be
Yeah, this is mine
Not your community
The laughter never reaches the eyes
A circle drawn in chalk with a quiet verdict lies
Every nod rehearsed, every glance a signal flare
If you're not born inside it, you're just passing air
They close to subtle victories, no one names allowed
A language made of absence, a silence worn proud
You thought it was connection, just a table, just a seat
But the flow beneath you shifted, you were never meant to eat
They don't raise their voices, they don't make it loud
Everything's changed
They never say no, they just never say yes
A master class in distance dressed up as finesse
Invitations drift past like ghosts in a hall
You're not excluded, just not counted at all
They study your rhythm, catalogue your tone
Then mirror it back like it was always their own
imitation while they tighten the thread you're speaking your truth they're deciding what spreads
it's not what they say
Is a weapon sharper than a decree, a tilt of a hat, a pause too long, and suddenly you're where you don't belong
No villain declared, no crime to defend, just a slow evaporation of where you once fit in
So you learn the quiet rules they never explain, don't show every card, don't echo their name
Let your persons be partial, let your edges stay blurred, mystery unsolved
I wish I
Where they crusade, comes pre-invented, if envy burn calories, they don't beat them, but here they come chewing glass again, they love saying he's bothered with a smirk and a shake while building old channels off the cr-
Okay
Hey, Joni, I'm sorry, hold on one second.
I got a call from my friend.
She wanted me to do a terror reading for her friend.
And so I was doing a terror reading for her friend
real quick over the phone.
How are you?
Joni, I don't hear you.
Is your mic working?
Here, I'm going there.
Let's see.
Does anyone hear her?
I don't hear her.
I'm loving it.
Joni.
She's up the way
Johnny
Wait, oh there you are. I hear you now. Hi
What I fell off the radar. Yeah, you fell you fell off. No, wait now. I lost. Oh gosh
Yes, Verizon commercial. Yeah, hi, we are you know, I didn't hear you for a second, but yeah, my friend. Wait, let me wait
Just did a just did a tear for my Russian friend. Oh, we have another guest on too. Okay. We've another guest coming up
Let's welcome. Oh, there you are. Here you are. Oh
My god, I'm in a Joni sandwich snap to there we go. Oh
Oh
What am I done? I'm confused. I'm lost in translation. I'll take it down. I'll take it. I'll take the other one down here. I can't hear you. Wait, let me turn my TV up.
Now do you hear me? Oh, you can hear me. Yeah, I hear you. Hi everybody. Sorry about that. I had a call. You don't hear me at all? You had a black eye? Are you in the black guy club?
Oh my God, I hear myself now. Okay, yeah.
Let's make sure it looks HD
Joining Baloney and psych alone a second. Why is my um, hold on
Wait, you came on to a two different your different counts. Okay, never mind. I'm just gonna talk to the TV
tell me if there's feedback because
Like my now my IP. I won't listen. Okay. Well, you're fine. I
Yeah, I think I hear myself a little in the back, but you're good. How are you? Do you hear me? Okay?
It's a little bit behind
I don't want that. Yeah, I don't need bologna and psycharone's
Oh, sorry, yeah, sorry guys, but I didn't my my Russian friend called and she had a Russian
Nancy is here. So Nancy, how are you? Yeah
So you look Joanie, I do have like I've never seen my necklace. I don't know if you see my necklace
It has Hebrew all over Nancy
Hold on. Let me see on the back of it. Oh, it's like see that right there
You see that, Joanie?
Q.
Stop it.
It's a little bit salty, but Q.
Don't do that.
You know, Kate would like-
Don't call you a Jew?
No, but Kate would like-
Fuck.
Okay, Kate wouldn't like-
I'm not allowed to call you a Jew?
Well, hey, John-
Okay.
I won't say anything.
But hey, be nice.
You don't know what you don't know.
Be nice to people.
But Kate wouldn't let you on because you're being racist, she said?
And what happened with that?
No, she didn't let me on because I came onto your panel.
That's why.
Oh.
And because you had Brandon Q on here, that's why.
Oh, yeah. Well, so what? I mean, I watched some of his stuff. It didn't look like it was. No, no, I agree. I agree. I mean, listen, I don't fuck with Brandon Q. I think he's a pedophile. But at the same time, it's your fucking stream. You can let whoever you went on. That's your fucking business. I don't care enough about this internet shit to be some sort of fucking like stream Nazi like this is who you can let on this for you can't let on. All I know is is when you really let them to go on, I will do.
Right. Okay. Well, it's fine. It's fine. Well, then that means that you should change the fucking subject and shut up of a Brandon Q and
People that start with J and
Did I nigger?
You just did you'll keep this loser. He's trying to get your shit fucked up and faggot
There you go. Three TOS is in a row
Okay, I'll be fine. Okay. Hey, I'll check them off. Okay. Hey, Joanie. I'm sorry about that.
Joanie?
I kicked them off. I kicked them off.
You know, that guy doesn't like you. He's trying to fuck your shit up, bro.
Yeah.
I'll be back.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. I'll be taking you out.
Yeah, so I'm gonna say I'm sorry about the Joanie. Like, it is crazy.
Yeah, like so, I mean, I have people saying don't go to my show now and but I don't I don't need most of the people that are like
not coming to my show like I don't think they are like very loyal anyway or just gonna listen to like
some loudmouth about how I'm trying to come with you. I don't know. Yeah, I just got to stick
about seeing my guns or else. Can you hear me now? I hear you fine. Yeah. John, John. Oh,
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank
See I hear you fine, but they hear my voice come like 10 seconds later. What would you hear?
Oh, I don't like that. Okay, wait, I'll try to figure it out. Okay, sweetie. I'll be back. I love you, sweetie
You please refrain from using that language. I'm right now, please. Okay
No, we can refrain from saying the n-word, but I'm still gonna call these motherfuckers out for what they are
Well, okay, that's fine. But how about this? We'll call them the cockamamie. That's okay. Perfect. Perfect. That works cockamamie ass
Mamie in blacks cockamamie blacks. Oh, okay. It's well
It's not even a it's not against to us
Yes, that's fine.
Say whatever, as long as you're not saying the N word, okay?
Perfect.
But how are you doing?
Did you watch last night's?
Oh, I'm doing fantastical, as I always am.
Fantastical?
Did you see last night's show?
It was pretty good.
Oh, look at there.
Look at there, Sandman in the chat.
Sandman was screaming today in the chat about,
oh, my God, you impressed me.
He's screaming at everybody everywhere.
Oh, my God, look at your eyes.
Oh, those are intense.
Okay, well
There's a kitty cat hi, hey, Alex
What up yo, Ronys if I sell you five dollars, can you give Q a reading?
Yeah, sir
Yeah, I'm gonna buy Q a reading cuz
But yeah, no no we don't point you so thank you take it to heart
I'm gonna show stuff up your ass one day. You're not gonna be good. I can't wait
Q come on. I'm getting jealous. Oh, no, don't read it till I give it to you
Oh
I just had a reading for a Russian and yeah, if you can give me a reading and you can accurately tell which star sign
I am like my horoscope sign, then I'll be an extreme
Aries or a Leo or something a fire. Nope right now. Okay. Oh, you're a Libra
Mm-hmm
Satisfy your fire sign not a fire sign. No, you're an earth sign
No
oh shit well you know maybe i don't know let me see you were closer with january okay well so you're
curious no your capricorn no january that's between sedentary is i said you were closer
with january okay okay so maybe you're a leaver you're not a leaver you said come on wooka come on
Okay, so you're a water slide, okay? What color eyes do you have?
Black.
Oh, here's black eyes, yeah.
Pretty dark, beyond brown, leave the dark dark.
Well, you know, what's funny? Can I just say he has no clue
And so just because I was I was goofing and made that song and was singing he categorized me and he put me like a
Haset what sort has said a ascetic Jew like the to the extremity and then he went there
And he has no clue my spiritual beliefs anything. That's like so sad man. I
Know I know I know but he's like you're a dirty Jew
Your your projection is for your own soul my friend. You're so sad like I like that makes no sense
Why would you come up and say something like that? No, I don't know. He's like he's a dick. I mean he's why I
Mean seriously if any any goodness he had he just like
Peed and pooped all over it. Yeah, what's up with that, dude words matter
He's a dick. He tells me terrible things and he got I know yeah, and then he doesn't even go back and go
Oh, I was just goofing. I'm just playing. I'm having a bad night. I'm stoned
Who's reading?
He's being a dick he's being a dick all right, but yo, can you just give me the I send you to stupid father on us?
Let's hit it
Three chords what does the pie dolls get tank or reading my court got the death card
He got the hangman. Sorry. Sorry. I didn't say that out loud. I'm sorry. I didn't mean I just think you know
Quiet on the set
In the past there's like this female it's a queen of cups and so there's this like very nurturing or like a female
That was pretty nurturing or something like that, but this one is kind of like on these cards
She was, I don't know, she was good at like, maybe a good cook or something like that, but she, um,
It was probably that bitch that kicked him out of the house
That's who he's talking about right now. Yeah. Yeah, the meth cooker. Yeah, the meth cooker
Yeah, exactly
Bb there you go, so
yeah and then also you were like and then maybe you were like wanting to go almost like you're kind of
wanting to go almost back like you're like kind of like drawn back to this where you were with
to whatever the past is like right now but it's like you know uh i think i'm drawn back to stick
my fucking dick in somebody's asshole oh my god exactly you're headed back to fucking vegan
Okay, thank you. Look at this. There's like, there's like, um, okay.
So there's like a lot of balance ahead of you. Like it's like you're,
and there's like almost like financial balance and like having like things.
Is that pot? Hockey pot? Hockey?
Because I'm going to balance my dick on somebody's head.
Can you mine please? Okay. Anyway, I'm just kidding. Okay. So anyway,
there's like, there's also like,
you have to turn into a porno reading joining.
I didn't pay for this,
I can't believe somebody hasn't put you in a fucking old folks home yet
Maybe your son or your daughter
Alright, so Karol is B because he was part of it
Let's go. It's the tank called reading.
Okay, yeah, easy.
Okay, thank God reading my old folks retirement home for this nigger
There is okay. There also is this queen of this queen of wands in the future
So she's like this person is like more passionate. I think this is like a maybe a better sexual match for you
No, it could be a fire sign or something like that
She's kind of scary looking too, but I'm yeah run. That's baby part to run bro
You're the one that tried to put something in my asshole, so I should be running from you
Oh my gosh.
Well, that's what the, so the polls are for us.
That's why there's polls there, you know?
I'm, I'm, I have that mask in the screen.
Oh no, no, no, no.
Okay, I know, I know, no, no.
Okay, it looks like this is a fucking day.
Queen, was that the queen of polls?
The queen of, of Cox, the queen of polls.
The queen of wands, the queen of polls is the queen of wands.
Joe Shipley said the same thing.
And we all seen what happened to Joe Shipley.
Well, look at this one. Also the moon. There's some kind of illusion. Remember when she's he's a ginger
Apple in the movie
Okay, I'm sure he would
But there's like some kind of yeah, he's been waiting speaking of Joe Shipley local car team of the moon and it's an orange
He's representing his orange pubic hair. He's been waiting to fuck a little twink. Just I get on play. This is staring
He's on point tonight
This is the greatest ringing ever!
Who is this witch? Who is this fucking wicked witch of the West?
Who am I? Balonies? You live my Balonies alone.
I literally am.
My Joanie Balonies.
Hold on, I'm scared to hear the rest of the reading.
Is this Christina's sister?
Yeah, there's an illusion around this woman like, there's a moon there and so there's
like some kind of deception or something like that. You have to be careful around this Queen
of Wands because you could be a witch or something like that because Queen of Wands
I don't like Blacks, you don't like Blacks.
That means Alexander Mayors, he mentioned Blacks.
That's what he's talking about there.
See, this is the greatest.
That's the main reason I don't like Black people is because of her.
Oh, come on.
Well, that's the main reason I like Black people because of her.
So that's weird.
Well, then you must like the stench.
Well, and here's your qq bro. You don't like the pink when you open the pussy lips
You started it
But whatever it is you're gonna see things from a different perspective too and also you're a kind of this monster
But you're like a kind of like a kind monster a little bit, but you're be like
But you might feel like you're trapped a little bit here or unable to move for a little bit, but you're also in your Emperor energy.
Also, oops, okay. Now also, maybe you're gonna regret something too because there's a spot like the Five of Cups is optimal say there's
Come on, regret. Maybe when you see things were perspective.
You okay, Joni? Let it out. I hear the fucking plum.
I got bubbles coming. Wait, I got bubbles coming out of my nose.
Hey, Gary. Come on, I got bounty for you, man.
Stop egging me on let him read
Okay, okay next car
For you're looking for this Queen of Swords who's gonna be like she's like a fairy kind of energy
That's Paige, bro. Get that bitch out of here. She has nothing to do with this.
Yeah, I'm gonna get my bolognese.
You should have stuck with the the black girl and the the entities from how
He's not here bro though you can stop reading
No, he's on overload. Look at him. He's going to read the whole deck. Let's go.
Next car. Let's go. We got 52 cars to go. Fuck that. A 52 car reading. Let's do it.
Oh, I got a 52 card reading.
Yeah, my money's worth tonight.
Why would you read my tarot deck like this?
It's like a six.
Oh, stop.
This is why I have to marry Joanie.
That laugh.
I need that laugh.
you understand? I need that. My left ear is popped. Breakfast, lunch, and dinner. I need that around.
Yo, Joni. Yo, Joni, if you start streaming, uh, Psyche will literally never have food.
Why what are you saying? Well, I'll never because then Alex is gonna donate all of his McDonald's money to you in psyche
Well, it's okay. It's okay. He can do. Oh
No, no
Me and Joanie are planning in the background. We're gonna buy him his own McDonald's
all right we're like we're right now we're painting the golden arches ourselves exactly
i just picked you with a bucket of paint that's so funny wait i'd never the long way through we got it
wait well what joni when were you in your prime
so the funny thing is I've never heard of a 52 card read
well he did tonight baby and it's still going on so let's mute him
that's not ruining it
it never stopped
card 22
card 22 and counting
that card looks like f***ing yoda
it's because we have his team of pentacles so there's like some kind of material
you're gonna do well materially get it
yeah it looks like tweetp bro that's tweetp
is the tweetp card
technically is material
Like because it's a it's a pentacles and so it vagina is material
Be the rule or you don't mean I was got the emperor for you to in this reading too
So it's like you're really gonna be doing materially better and it looks like you have this woman who's actually the queen on the queen of
Stores she might be an airside and she's like she might be a
I'm saying maybe the divorce save woman that
Might convince your future and I know as soon as she heard this reading she divorced me. Oh come on stop
Can I get married I can I marry you? Oh my god. Listen guys. I got a gold dime
Are you done? Are you? Are we on what card?
Yeah, he looks like baby Yoda and I'm not worried about like, you know
I'm gonna say something I'm gonna say something to this cute the cute character guy this keep whatever the cute guy
I want to say a baby girl
I want to say this to you for real, for real. Okay. Keep them separated. No, just kidding.
But what I want to say to you is I told Saga the Sailor, I said, you know,
that guy, when you showed your, your cat, you know, stretched out and everything,
I know you got to be good people underneath all the riff and the raft. There's no way that you
could be what you're some of the words that are coming out. And I get it, but there is a cat.
Oh, he does not. He does not. He's very good.
I beat him every time, every time they make me mad.
Yep.
Macamera in the face.
More deflection.
Oh, you don't want to be seen as sweet at all, do you?
No, I want to be seen as a mean cuckoo.
Yeah, but we see through you.
Yeah.
We just unmasked you.
I bet he cuddled with them.
I bet he would cuddled.
No.
Well, wait a minute now.
Yeah, calm down there, butthole bud.
slow your roll, pull up your speedo.
Bad boys club.
Calm down there.
Just because the ladies are lovin' on me
doesn't mean you need to come step in, okay?
Okay, I'll get a sex change.
If you want me to have a sex change, I'll do it.
Oh, no.
Yeah, well, they better get better at making pussies then.
Ay, fey.
Wait, I didn't mean to say that.
I know I son should've.
I'll buy one of those.
rubber pussies and then you can oh I never fucked me uh mtf but I ain't willing to try
Okay. I like that. Perfect. This makes me want to make this pretty sick about Jammer.
You know, Psyche, you know, when you say that, unfortunately, even though you're joking,
now I have a visual of a rubber pussy, like, oops, VJJ. I don't want to. I don't want to,
but it happens. I heard, like, you know, Barry was on... Like, his asshole is a rubber pussy.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. No, it isn't.
You know, Barry said that, Barry on, on case I, on case you heard that, Barry said,
Samman has a picture of my dick in a, in a, in a pocket pussy and a picture of my ass.
And he downloads it.
What?
What do you expect when you send your news to Samman, Barry?
I mean, come on, stop sending your news to them.
Of course he's going to download them.
He's gay.
Listen, all these black people on here are gay.
That's why they obsess over you, Samman.
I got you, Emeril.
A lot of black people are gay, but most trainees are black.
Just saying.
true it's true it actually is true there are a lot because you know i don't know there's a lot of
um damage the last time you ran into a white tranny never well white tranny anything like the closest
they're either fucking latina or black most of the time how do you know from personal experience
you must be deep enhancing them just because i live because i because i live on the blade
The blade is the area of the city where all the fucking hookers are
No, no, he like ran into this black gay guy and the black he was like his best friend when he was like when he was out
And wherever you were we're in California. Oh, it wasn't my best friend. He was a good. Yeah
He was like, but he was so nice and the guy loved he's like
Michael Michael basically like a drag queen a little bit
Almost he was a black homeless man because I was homeless at the time
I did watch that stream the night that you went up to get, remember you went up and got
like one thing, one drinky poo, and then you're walking home and you gave a guy a dollar.
I saw that stream that night.
That was like recently.
That was recently.
Remember that?
Yeah.
That was recently.
No, he's talking about the stream where I went up to the homeless man and maced him.
Yeah.
He's talking about that.
Okay.
That's a whole different story.
You didn't make the homeless guy, and that was a kind of classic episode.
Well, it was a homeless guy that I had fucking lived with and I trusted with all my shit,
and then he went through my entire bag and like, and got rid of all my clothes.
So I went back there and I fucking raised hell.
So there's more to this story versus just listening from the time to walk up there and Mesa. Yeah, right, right?
Well, thank you for explaining because I was like
When he did it he then he started running away and he's like God forgive me
I told him I told him before I did it that I was gonna do it and I didn't run away
No, I only started running because VB fucking pulled up on me and was trying to call the cops on me
So I got an Uber out of there. Yeah
Well, he had all of a sudden, Joni, you see this woman in a truck just come across the
median of the road for him and get in the car and he's like, I'm not getting in the
car with you.
And then it was pretty funny.
You can't make that up.
Imagine if I would have gotten in the car.
It was crazy.
Joni, it was crazy.
It sounded scripted weird, but it was real, real.
It was real.
It was crazy.
That's something.
Yeah, it was.
But then I think, was that the turning point of when you kind of like got out of there,
Like no, I got not I got out of there like a couple weeks before that because she kicked me out of there because I
She told me that I I couldn't smoke weed in the house anymore perfectly fine. Whatever no big deal
So then I started going out to the back porch to smoke weed
But you know, I smoke a lot of fucking weed so I was going in and out a lot
Then it became a fucking issue. Oh, you keep going in and out this and that and then finally I was just like shut up
So like that's
Like what was the problem the way the door slid open the door shut the in and out
No, the problem is if that bb smokes meth and she gets paranoid. That's a problem
That's quite a problem my friend. That's it. I mean come on now
I mean, maybe if she stopped smoking fucking meth it wouldn't have been an issue. Right. Right. I'm cute at that point. She was tweaking
And what happens to you at that point, though,
then from there, where did you go?
Like, after that, the main thing?
Oh, I went to, so when VB kicked me out,
I went to fucking sleep in the tent,
and then I was still working my job,
so I would wake up every day.
Like, nothing ever happened,
and I would go to my job and I would work it,
and then I would come back for like two weeks.
To literally a tent I was living in a fucking tent and then
Wow, I met my roommate at the library because that's the best. That's where you get that when you're homeless
That's the only place you can charge is at the library and use their computers and yeah
I met my fucking roommate at the library and I've been here ever since how long ago was that mask
Hey, that was
September of last year.
Oh, so it was kind of recent.
You went through a lot.
Oh, yeah.
And he's from Pittsburgh,
um, Joni and he's,
and I was in California.
So he's come across the country, you know. Wow. So are you here like are you in a good space now?
You're here to stay are you kind of still like the next I mean, I'm not I don't know if I'm gonna stay in California my whole life
No, I know
Oh, yeah, I've been living in the same place for fucking since September, so
How is he like you
Seiki and you like five guys in and out. So but no, how's it in and out is way better than fucking five guys. I
I
Came to the West Coast and in out is a hundred times better than fucking five guys
It's been a while since I had five guys, but it was always no matter like it was always so bland no matter how much shit
I don't fucking like smash burgers
I don't know what the trend is about smash burgers these days, but I don't fucking like that shit
Yeah, I want my burgers to be thick juicy. Yeah, I get it very good
And I don't like smash burgers. It's weird like oh, yeah
I'm gonna put my I'm gonna put the patty on the grill and then smash the living shit out of all the juice out of it
Right. I get it. Yeah
They kind of dry we just have a smash burger across the street. I never went there because it was like I mean they're not
Apparently if you do it right they say it's not dry
But I mean I would like I would still much rather have a burger that wasn't smashed than one that was
Even a fat burger fat burger is good. There's a fat place. No, I've never had the
Seen a fat burger in real life. I don't know if they have this all over. I only heard about that in movies
You heard a steak and shake
Yeah, so back in the day, I thought it was only where I live in Missouri.
So like, you know, like my grandpa, my dad, like it's like history.
Now we don't have any, like they all closed, except I think one.
Okay.
Where I'm from, they all closed too.
And those were my favorite fries.
They had like the shoestring really in fries, but you're talking about, I remember, you
remember, well, back in the day, you'd sit on the stool, like a diner, and then they have
or, you know what I mean, where they put the square like piece of red meat and then they
would put like a little iron on it where it smashes it.
Yeah, and smash it down.
But is that different than the smash burger?
Because I'm thinking.
No, no, no, smash burgers, that's literally what that means is like, well, well, no, technically,
technically, a smash burger is when you have like a round ball of ground beef on your,
on the, on the metal, on the metal smasher and then you smash it onto the grill.
Right.
Well, that's what's, okay.
I got it.
Yeah, but there's
Starts off it has to start off as like a round ball of meat and then you smash it
Yeah
And then they they closed and then I heard that Freddy. Is it Freddy's? I don't know if you have that here
We don't have that in and out
It's Freddy and then here. What do we have shake and shack shack shake?
Shake shack or something. Yeah, it's kind of expect. Yeah, shake. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, Shake Shack is expensive as fuck and this line is always fun as fuck line
So I get a door dash, which is a nightmare, but I'm sure when you go in there the line is probably to the door
Yeah
Like I wanted I wanted to try Shake Shack so bad when I was in New York City
When I was a man and the line was always to the fucking door. I was like crazy. I'm not waiting an hour for a burger
I'm sorry, right
Yeah, well, that's where the New York City where you can get pizza like any time you want fuck that
So when you go with pizza, I'd like to you know, there's all kinds of crusts I'm in St. Louis
So I'm like, you know, even though I like that somewhat thick, but I'm I'm probably one you don't like on the thin crust one
And we have something called Provelled cheese. You ever heard of that?
Provell tastes like Velveeta, but it's white, but it's very good. Like Provellone short for Provellone. No, no, no
Provellone's like stinky stinky. I like stinky cheeses. Provellone, no, no, no, no, Provellone's not stinky. You got the wrong one
So the stinky one is Munster. Oh, yeah, Munster, she's, yeah. Oh, Munster. She stinks like shit.
Provellone's fine as long as you don't leave it out all night. As long as you don't leave the Provellone out all night, you're good.
Well some people can't stand like the blue cheese, but see I learned to like it
You know like because that's gross too, but like the real made tag blue cheese that crumbled like that's really good stuff
Especially be dipping in the chicken wing like the spicy chicken wing or something
I'm just saying you know you could go with this recently like in the last year
I learned about Gouda and how good like Gouda might be the best cheese
It might be the best one that I've ever had so far. I love that shit. It's so fucking good
I could eat a whole fucking block of it
I know she's so good
Wonder if anybody I wonder if there's ever like a child a child named Gouda like not Buddha not Yoda
Gouda like I wonder if anyone's ever named their child
I mean somebody named their child fucking beat up before
I'm sorry, not laughing, but that was funny. Sorry, is that really real though? I mean
I'm sure somebody's named their child shithead before
They named it fucking gg allen jesus allen place like listen listen listen listen to me
So you know like when people do name their kids, whatever kids, whatever
They're like, you don't realize it,
but you put a personality to it.
So like, even if they're not that,
you kind of fuck with them,
because then they become that in your mind's eye.
Does that make sense?
So like, right?
So.
No name.
I know, they named me fucking Judah.
Years of therapy later.
Just kidding.
Yeah, wow.
I'm laughing with you not at you and all and all of my family
They're all roman catholics and they still name me judo. Oh my god, right?
Well, I'll dare they
You know your real name, but I'll be all no i'm just kidding. My name is james. Oh, yeah
Oh james
I didn't get a Hebrew name. They call you Jimmy, but not Judah
I'm John like so they didn't mark James Luke and John John Mark Matthew Mark Luke and John Matthew John Luke Mark James
Peter
I'm named after a Joseph. Does that count? Yeah, you are Josephina
Yeah, no, wait, wasn't a father named Joseph the father of God or something. I don't know
Jesus's father was tech. Well, not well. No, Jesus's father was God, but Mary Mary
Mary like the Virgin Mary her
Spouse was Joseph. Yeah, the carpenter Joseph the carpenter
I'm so close to singing but I won't because I can't sing but the all those songs are
You want to sing some hymns, and I don't know about hymns the hymn in my pants
No, not that how about this Mary did you know
Catholic church where we had organs and they play organs organs. Well, I like there was an organ player
Tulips on my organ
It was super fucking old school like that's not some really old school like too old
Like there was an Oregon player. We had kneelers. We had to see we had to kneel
All the hymns
Goodness that's a lot
Yep. No, I mean that wasn't it was normal though. I went to Cali. No, I know I get it
That's what we did that every every Wednesday. We went to church. I get it
But I like like that one like well, what's a group pin pinnatex was that a pin?
No, not pinnacle. No the group. They look pinnatex
Penta is like are they a religious group? But they don't know no the one that's in Mary. Did you know you're baby?
Then I like that song or like
Hallelujah. No, that's in you can't play fucking gospel music with anything besides an organ. It's
Oh, so they're one of the cat named Katie's dirty sinners.
Katie says, oh, yes, my God is an awesome God.
That's a sin.
My God is an awesome God.
He reigns from.
Yeah, that's a sin.
But it's.
Oh, that song says who says who.
Yeah, no, I'm just my when I was so silly when I was a teenager my dad actually played like he was a guitarist in a fucking
Church band so instead of like I went from fucking organs to this dude playing in a church band with a guitar and shit
Because of the whole time when I was growing up like they kind of made it seem like
Like, we do the organ thing, and then the blacks do the fucking Baptist church with the band and that whole thing.
Right.
So then when I, then I get to be a little bit older than I realize, no, fucking white people do that shit, too, and have fucking bands and tambourines and shit in the crowd.
Yeah.
I like to play with organs.
Well, I just, like, said it, so on my mind, do you remember the Blues Brothers? Was there a movie coming out?
I'll rearrange your organs, bitch.
Oh.
Oh, yeah, I'd love that.
Uh, I don't know.
Your mouth.
Okay, I'll stop it. You went from like the church organ or organ. Wait, how do I make the difference between an organ in your body and the organ in your, you know what?
It's an organ.
It's literally the same. It's all the same word, but in a different like mean meaning. Yeah, welcome to English
Is this your first day speaking English?
Yes, it is. Don't make me like you
I'm starting to like it now. I'm starting to understand the lore. Uh-oh. Uh-oh
Yeah, once you get past like the the beginning and you peel a little bit. He's not too bad that one
right
So now I get it.
That's cool.
I had to get past the, you know, get in the oven, put comments, but then once I got past that,
you know, and then he started telling me a story, then it started like unfurling. Is it like, you
know, like a flag, camera? He grows on you. He grows on you. He grows. Not like like genital
words. No, I mean, not like, yeah, like our tags that you get removed. But you're the one that
brought that up. You must have experience with it. Yeah, so I must. I think I used that on you.
And I said, you must have it.
Oh my God, us humans are funny.
Yeah.
Oh, can I add?
Let's talk about,
let's talk about your Jenin awards then.
Never had them.
Thank you very much.
Do you know anything about birds?
Uh, you mean the ones, the government ones, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
But so I just looked at my door the other night and literally I like overnight
Like I have a wreath out there like a like a wreath right by like I have a sliding glass door
I have a cat right that goes in and out and there's a wreath like right by the opening of my door
And I look and I and I looked up there and there's a little baby nest that they must have built and there's a little like a
Little lady. I guess it's a woman one a girl. Yeah, you need to take a stick or a bat and take that shit out
Oh, no, but it's weird because you know how birds don't like they come like
What they like Babe Ruth, he's like a baseball, but yeah, Babe Ruth that fucking nest
No, I don't know what to do. I'm like because it's too late that Natalie's the nest there
So usually they say if you if you touch the eggs and the birds, it's all good like the mother will look
Yeah, I know touch the eggs and touch the birds
It's like all day I kept looking out. I didn't see no bird and it was raining and everything and then
Actually, they say you're supposed to spit on your hand and then touch the eggs. You're talking about
No
Sorry, I went there. Sorry. No
No, but like right now if I go out there and I look up there. I see a silhouette
Oh, John. Oh, excuse me. I keep calling psyche seeing it like he like he's just stoic
And I don't know if he's sleeping. He's just sitting there. Wait. Do you know him in real life?
Who?
Me.
Of course, I do.
Not like touch the shoulder.
You know him in real life?
Does he stink?
No.
I know his...
I just...
We're like...
I just don't.
Well, you keep calling him by his first name, so you must have like a real, like a real
some sort of association.
My aunt's my aunt Joanie.
Is my aunt Joanie.
Am I aunt Joanie?
Bitter aunt Joanie?
Yes.
Do you have a ball sack? Yeah, yes, I have three I have three balls. Oh my god. That's a good answer. Yeah
What do you want me to say? That's so lafield. I'm really talking. Are you born in were you born before?
1980 or after
before be be I
Know I can hear it in your for before
I can hear the the pre gas tax in your voice. Oh come on the pre what the gas gas
It's okay, I forgive you
Your your shall I say weirdo? No, I didn't say that out loud. It's okay
We all have our voice. It's a weirdo, but it's I like that about we're all right
We all have our own voice can't can't disguise it. Yeah, at least you don't sound like Christine
Yeah. Oh yeah, thank you.
She doesn't, Christina.
Stop it. You're going to scratch your throat again.
Christina was like, oh, he's going to lose his voice today.
He keeps imitating me.
Saiki, have you read the YouTube DOS?
She said that to me. She said that to me.
I'm like, no, I have not.
I don't really need to know if somebody tells me you read the YouTube TS
I just want to like reach through the fucking phone and grab you by your fucking neck and strangle you like
YouTube TS. What are you a fucking will you are a volunteer police officer, huh? I hate that shit. Let's work for YouTube. Oh
I'm here. Oh, I'm here to
YouTube would love to hear about this like shut the fuck up
Yeah, well, since it's Christina, I don't find that you say that because she's bringing the millionaires at Google would love to hear about the debauchery you're getting into on YouTube.
Fucking weirdo.
Yeah, oh, I think and thank you for thank you. I got a donation. I want to thank that up to the person that donated
I just wanted to thank you because it was me because people are gonna get attacked right now by their channel
I'm not I'm just gonna keep the donations anonymous and I donated you like a hundred dollars and you don't even
I do appreciate thank you
Fuck is wrong with you, dude
My hundred dollars doesn't matter or something. I'm gonna give you a big matters big kisses. Thank you. Thank you so much
I only live an hour away from Stike, so I'm going to go there and I'm going to make him
into my sleeve.
I'm gonna make you into my slave psyche and you're gonna you know your trust fund will pay all the bills and
I'll buy you burgers everyone to know
I will be your slave, but I'll tell you why you McDonald's here now
People make bad slaves because we're just like lazy. We don't we won't be like I'll do it later and stuff and like you know
Why people are possible to deal with but I'll be your slave. I will I will you can do whatever you want
Oh, so that's what you think now until I pull out that fucking belt
Oh, no, okay. Wait, wait, I don't want to be part of it. Oh, yeah, you might like that. Sorry
BB gun, I'll pull out the BB gun
Oh, come on.
Just shoot it at my butt.
OK, that's it.
That's it.
Right?
Moon walking backwards off the stage.
But before I go, I wanted to ask you one more question.
I wanted to know, since the musical stuff joking aside,
does that make you want to play an instrument,
learn how to, the drums, the guitar, saxophone, flute,
harmonica?
Thank you for trying to teach me how to play the skin flute.
Okay, all right, all right, but then I was like leave me alone you dirty bastard
Oh, my God. Oh, he's the best.
He's the best skin flu player the side of the.
No, no, no.
You're basically you're basically like the Beethoven of the skin flu.
Yes.
Well, I do.
Do you have to say it because I had to go visual again?
Then I have to know like how like the way you're going to leave.
And I'm going here in there.
You don't have nothing to do.
Woman, you're retired.
What?
You know, she could do.
Here's just make it shit up. He doesn't know anything. Okay. You're retired
Retarded he's calling me retired
You're retired you don't have a job you don't have nothing to do tomorrow
You don't have no reason to do nothing. So just like shut your horn mouth up and scan the panel you
Q that's very rude. What's wrong with that?
You got to meet the need so you might be talking as one of his other panelists that's been over the
That's not me
Okay
Well
That'd be hard for what maybe five and a half on a good day
Okay, that works.
Hey, Q is just pissing out.
Maybe six and a half if I, you know, if she goes in real life.
Some time.
I go.
Have you ever seen something like a fucking horse or it's in the horse though. There's people. So you see a dick and you go
Yeah, I go
Then there's people that do a horse bondage and they dress like horses
I've ever seen that they get to look that up sometime on the internet
They they go and they think they were okay. Yes, I'm seeing that before I don't want to get put on the list
You don't want to be put on the list? Yeah, but I think yeah, I don't want to get put on
Actually, but there's really it's really I'm disturbing these people that made it. Yeah, I saw that before
That's almost where that's almost as bad as looking up fucking Jose Xander's dick
Who's Jose Xander?
You don't know who Jose Sanders. Oh, yeah, I know him. I remember him
It's been a while since I watched it the one that was like a travels around and he was yeah
He's like a vagabond, and he's in drugs. Is he still is he still out there?
Okay, so actually somehow some way he managed to get himself a car through some program
Now he just like does uber and shit like does he have that dog still?
I think so, I'm not 100%
I don't keep up on Jose like that
Jose goes through dogs, Jose
goes through dogs more often than I clip
my fucking toenails, so I don't know
I've seen Jose
in the time that I've known him, I've seen Jose
go through like three dogs, and I've only known this
motherfucker for like three years
What happens to the dogs?
You don't know about, he had a dog named
for example, he had a dog named Cypress
he couldn't afford whatever surgery or like issue that the dog had and so he
basically just like let the dog die because he couldn't you know he was how
he's a homeless guy doesn't have any money and the dog had an issue like some
sort of heart issue and he just like let the dog die oh that's horrible but he's
that he's one of those homeless dudes who like he'll use a dog for the sympathy
and for the donation bait so like when he has a car I doubt he has a dog now I
This would be the time well, I guess at least they'd have a bed sitting in the car. I don't know
Yeah, but then even on top of that like if you're ubering and doing door-dashing shit with a dog in the car
Like yeah, this is a recipe for disaster. Right, right
Yeah, like remember having a vegan patriot her dog. Yeah, I remember that. Yeah
Hey Amber you want to talk about my small dick you literally you're fucking you're
40 years old and your husband is 75 like I don't want to hear nothing about dicks your husband's dick can't even get hard anymore
My goodness
Your husband's dick is literally like the fucking like whenever you have one of those like straws
There's like the slinky end of it that bends
There you go
How what is yours? No, it's not yikes. We've listened. We've known this about Amber for a long time. She's she's I
Don't know
Then I'll be honest with you. She's into fucking
Blacks and old men
Okay, so
So she's a night rider and a fucking elderly rider
Who cares? I miss on it was she's not breaking the law, right?
No, no, she breaks the law pretty frequently. You must not know. I don't know any. Yeah, I don't know
I'm more of what you call normie breaks the law quite frequently
She smokes a lot of meth and then she's gotten caught multiple times
There's a body cam footage and all this Amber. You're lucky. My channel just got deleted your fucking body cam footage a
Part of your body cam footage archive is gone now because my channel got deleted
It's the same I pretty much I pretty much got my my handle back there because instead of using an L
I used a capital I so it's pretty much the same thing.
Your handle.
Yeah, like my app, you know, and chat like at whatever.
Yeah, I was thinking of like, did they use to have like a big jug of booze and they called it a handle.
Pretty much anything over a fifth is pretty much a handle or anything over a leader is a handle. Yeah, I
Don't drink liquor that much
What do you drink? I saw you. What did you drink beer?
You like those twisted teas, I think. Oh, okay
Quick the teas are my favorite, but I can't I that's like a once in a while thing for me
Most time I just drink beer if I drink twisted teas the way that I drink beer. I'd have diabetes
Yeah, I have a heart eliminated tonight
Here's my I like those two. Those are cool. Oh
My god, my cat is going berserk rip pineapple
It's that time of night. That's no, there's a bird. There's a bird. Well, yeah
He does this anyway, but I have the door closed like I told you I was trying to tell you there's a
Mama bird that's alright. He's out there. He can't get to it, but I'm I'm nervous kind of about it
Like this I can't even
I can't even let these two n-words in the fuckin' in my room in the morning because they're
so annoying about the birds and all that stuff.
Right.
And all night long he's running around like I can't sleep like it's crazy why they get
up and run all night.
And they make that stupid fuckin' noise like they're like I don't know like what the hell
were Edith Bunkers in the house.
Just kidding.
Watch it.
I mean oh I'm not alone why do they do that I wonder.
Oh, he's running right now, that's like their most active times are late at night early in the morning, right?
I want my cat to sound like Rudy. Yeah, there's a little
Wait like like 12 more years. Yeah, right. I know
Okay, then they finally get old and they chill but then you know when they're like I have you like based
My two are like still kittens
And they're they go nuts. They go I've seen them go absolutely crazy
They've now started to fight each other sometimes
They get pissed off each other and I got to like separate them
They cut a field mouse
Their brother their brother and sister and they've they grew up with each other like
Like their whole life. They've only really known each other, but um
Yeah, they they they fight and fucking the one always hisses at the other and I don't want their her face to get all fucked up
So yeah
Gotta like separate them out the room and like let them calm down. I don't even I don't know if I could
I mean if I was gonna have to they have to either get along or at least be in separate
Now I wouldn't want to separate that that's too much to me unless well if they're just kittens
Maybe they need more time, but I don't know they're kids, but they're not like they're not like like kittens like you're thinking of they're like yeah
They're eight months nine months old. So they're like cats, you know what I mean? They're they're cats
They're they're like damn near grown. They're just
Are they the same sex or opposites?
Opposites opposite, okay
Their brother and sister
Ginger and Luna and Luna's the girl and ginger's the boy, right? Yeah Luna is here curled up in a ball
I don't know if he can
Oh, I know. It's looking at my face. Okay. I'm trying to turn it around like that. Yeah.
Luna. Luna. Luna has grown up in a ball. Gracie. Oh, it's a ball.
So, do you cut the nails yourself or do you take them to the vet?
I know I know I get it but I but still when if they well a long time ago nails they lose nails
What do you mean like shutting the shutting pieces or whatever?
Yeah, I mean they don't yeah, I
Mean the years of that. I know back in the day they would come like with their little nails
I know they don't do it anymore. They would be the clawed
Which is really sweet other than the pain because when they give you make biscuits on you
It's like oh, that feels good a little massage. I know and this bitch will make biscuits on me and it hurts
Right
I know and this one bites me too. It's like outs. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You just see
What happened?
Katie says tell her to cut back on the carbs and sugar
It's okay. Okay, John is not okay
John is not called toilet because it has one invent of the toilet the 800s and his name is John crapper. I think
But it's like not mean it's not named after that the John's are not enough for the toilet the toilets in after a John
The Porta John. Yeah, I'm sorry. Yeah, the Porta John. Yeah
Yeah, you have some yeah, Nancy says I have one of my son's cats named Pearl
He's pet you one time and then you turn into a fucking monster
Now you just want petted all the damn base
What do you feed your cats wet and dry?
I started off wet because well when I first got them they were like too small to even eat dry food, right?
Now I just give that have like it's kitten dry food. I give them like the meow mix kitten stuff. Yeah
Maybe we have another guest coming up. Let's welcome McQueen
Thank you. I love the welcoming.
He's so nice. Let's welcome him.
But why don't you name that sort of toilet?
I got that joke from you, Dick.
Honestly, you said that like two weeks ago and I was laughing so hard.
You probably don't even remember it.
It was one of those like when you know you're going to store.
And you're like, my name is John. I'm in NAFTA fucking toilet. And that made my day. I left so hard
You try to be gay or does it come naturally? It comes naturally, but I thought about it and I'm like
Isn't John the Baptist John aren't they like the figures in the Bible?
Well, there's there's the 12 there's the 12 fucking apostles like
Matthew one of his name John John
Like meaning
Yeah, there's a the toilet is named after somebody named John Crapper who invented the toilet
John Crapper. Okay. Now we're getting someone. I don't know John. No, Johnny, you can't leave things like that out
I need those facts. There's a John the Crapper. John. No, there isn't
He just said it the invent of the toilet. Yes. He did in like the 1800s inside. Oh, Luna
Are you serious? Is that why they call it the one of the John? I'm gonna put you outside. Are you joking psych?
No, I swear to God. I can look it up right now. Let me see
to the
top of the
I don't know what I'm saying.
Jesus Christ.
Come on.
The origin of the word crap.
Has it been claimed in popular?
Oh my.
Luna, I'm going to put you on.
I'm going to put you on.
He's gonna go down the whole lineage Peter, and just kidding exactly Peter the frapper like big the gig is up
your name's after a toilet a so
Like you're not gonna get out of this one. His name is John Bemis. You're actually taking a big a hole with the crapper thing
Interesting trivia question like hey McDonald's before they close so pony up motherfucker
It's Tony a motherfucker. Where's it? Where's your money at Alex? Oh, it's three. Okay. It's two one in the morning
I spend it behind you a fucking reading you don't you remember? Yeah, McDonald's is open most some places
It's open. Well, I think where he's at. It's open 24 seven. Oh, no, no, no
He's there's two there's two there's one that closes early and the one that's a little farther away. I forget you live there, too
No, but I used to
Do you live in California now?
No, no.
I'm just, you know,
my last name is Dash or Steen.
Back in the day, you know, in another life.
Door dash sucks, bro.
They keep talking to me.
The dash pass thing.
You don't know how to do it right.
Broski, you don't know how to do it right.
I'm going to send it to you.
You were a fucking Jew?
Oh, come on cute say nice a nice, but um, no you said her name was steen. Yeah, I was joking. She's joking
She's joking. She said she said it's better be fucking joking. He's a dasher steen
I don't like juice. Oh
You don't even know
Come on. That's terrible. I never said nothing about it. But even but here's
Wait, here's what I'll leave you with. What do you know? Not not just because some like just like I'd say I don't like
Catholics or I don't like Christians or I don't like this. I don't like humans though. That's so stupid.
You're classifying people by like dumb things. They're just humans and so when they get naked
They shit, they pee, they bleed just like you, they're just human, like I don't like
them, you're just extremes in all of them, you're basically meeting yourself.
There are different human beings.
That's bullshit.
I'm sorry.
No, but I'm saying, if you're Jewish, there's extremes.
What the hell are you?
I don't like Jewish.
I don't like Jews.
I'm just talking, I'm talking about those cruel human, weird hat-wearing motherfuckers.
Yo, that's an Orthodox Jew.
Yeah, like a real fucking, like, aesthetic Jew.
Yes, yes.
That's the problem.
See?
I agree with you fell into the trap of classifying others. Oh, you don't know that's the way the division in the planet comes in
You guys fell for that shit. You're a Jew. You're this you're that
Everybody that I'm that I share the planet with me was just another human
Thank you. I'm sorry
It was paying just like you
Exactly
You're hating on humans
How can you are you sure you can say that?
Or in a higher level
You I know you got a answer for if not now
later.
Brother, you know if I was God, you know what I would do. You know what I would do, bro
Put some sense into me. I can roll. I would grab one of every race on the planet
German Nazi white black Jew Hindu Hispanic Mexican every race on the planet
Ideology is because of amber in the chat that
next to each other and strip them naked and say look next to you, bro
You're not
Pakistan the Indian the German the Russian the American the anything the North Korean you're all the fucking same
Oh
You have a little pee pee and your kids and you shit and you eat your hunger
Shit is made to the virus
You what type of Mexican are you
I don't think I've like I've ever said those words. I like that we're in a white
fucking line, bro. That's the game. Really? You really wearing a white you really talk like that?
Don't you notice how all the religions are the same thing? It's just a different book. I like the
Quran, the Bible, your Judaism, Hinduism, right? But at the end of the day, they will believe in
the same thing. One higher power.
they all implode on each other against each other just like
what's going on in our world. Yeah, that's the government's
game. So separated everybody with religion separated. So when
you're on a subway train, next to somebody you look at them like
look at that dirty Indian. And they look at you like look at a
dirty Caucasian. And bro, you're just humans. Right. Fuck up
with that bullshit.
until you fall down, and one day you might have to have somebody raise you up, and it happens to be in the investigation.
Alex, haven't you ever had to change train tires because some of them just smell so fucking bad?
Like, come on.
Know you live in New York City. I know you smell those people. They well look a lot of I will say this
I used to cut you know cut hair and like depending on the culture like if they eat a lot of
Something that comes right through the skin. It's not even like it isn't like they smell, but it's just like dog shit
But like it's even if you're Italian you like say you ate
When you are homeless you just said you
Italians don't eat enough garlic for it to like come through our skin
I'm just saying religion is a fucking facade right shit to control the masses
The war and I ran all this shit is happening because of religion right exactly and then they want the end of
I don't want to go there. You just hate when I was homeless. I still hated blacks
But you like that black at Michael
Same thing, bro. Black, white, the skin is my deal and I hope I hope the god that he fucking found some like
Way off the street
I know that too, that's true. It's like that's it's like just like people are probably in prison
Wait, he was Mexican. He was not Mexican. No, come on. Of course he is
I don't know what he is. He looks like some Spanish dude
Like an overgrown
It looks like an overgrown
Honduras Roni, did you ever see Shawshank?
That's my name
I'm calling you Roni. Did you ever see Shawshank Redemption?
Yes, okay. So that was a great movie. So, but remember when the one guy they was in jail
So not jail prison so long that when he got out he didn't
Institutional line they remember he was scared of the real world
Right, what's your point?
No, I just I was just saying of you're like sometimes you're caged and you were saying something that reminded me of that movie
That like you might be in there and you won't you think you want to be free, but after a while
Like what freedom is and everything.
And sometimes you could sit in jail.
So fucking that's the saddest part of that movie.
Is that 100% that's the death of that movie.
What the fuck?
What do you got?
Yeah, that was that.
See, I don't want you to just want the party.
I think he was the.
I think he went to a library, the librarian or something
in prison and like that gave him like purpose.
And he was done out of prison and he had no fucking purpose and he was bagging groceries
In the world and when he went in it was in 1930 now it's 1990
He was old as fuck. So I mean, yeah, if you I'm sure if you come out when you're like 50
It's different than when you come out. He was the best
Yeah, you still got a little light in the pencil a couple, you know, that you know, wait a minute. Wait, wait
You guys the best scene in my when he said the word obtuse
Remember that obtuse that bring about.
and when he was like he was working from you know i'm talking about the character that came in
you know that guy i forget his the names now but like and he was doing like he goes and shine my
shoes remember and he every night he had to put the bible and went in the bookkeeping in the safe
and that one night he said and you know something something and he whistled and he walked out the
door and the guy sat there and he put a little note in the bible and you see him walking and he's
And then at the very last scene, he opened up the box, right?
And he had like those dirty shoes before they would like shot him and everything.
It was like the best.
So there's such a great show.
Yeah. No, my favorite was when they found the poster in the hole.
The poster.
The man just disappeared like a part of the wind.
Right. Right.
Like, Rachel, I look at you fancy pants.
I mean, the best part is whenever, whenever they figure out that he fucked over their taxes, like he.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And they like they're like their faces when they realized that he fucked them all over and then like crawled through a shithole to get out of there
I think literally has shit to
I thought that it was I thought that was a true story like Danny my whole life up until like
There's a movie though. It was you probably it may be before your times
But it was really good to and I had Robert Redford who's dead now, but it was called brew Baker. You ever heard of that?
If you can look it up, it's like it's kind of like that too as well
And it's like it's like the inside like goes against and what's patriotic
It's like kind of deep meanings like blah blah blah, but it's really good. I love that kind of Robert Redford, huh?
Yeah, Robert. I'm showing your age there. No, my favorite fucking prison movie of all time is cool hand Luke
I was just here to say, cool hand Luke, how many eggs can you fit in your mouth?
I think it was 72, I never seen that either, it was done stupid, it was done like really stupid,
but I figured you would fucking like go at me about it.
It was done really stupid, I can't remember, I'm shaking a boss.
Remember when you run with the leaf, right?
It was the, that was the, oh my God, that was a cool hand Luke is such a good movie.
That's one of the first movies that's like, like, how do I say it?
I can still enjoy it, but it's not too old to where it's, like, dated, you know?
When you watch movies from the 50s, you're like, ah, this is like, I can't even relate to any of this tumor or any of this at all.
Right, right, right, right, right, no, no.
But I think the 70s is like, is like where I can kind of like start to...
Kind of be normal, you know, and the 60s shit was like still black and white and it's like candy with shots like a whole different
70s comes a long
People are smoking weed and stuff like you know things are kind of normalized in the 70s
Yeah, oh and cool and Luke and he said when they took him out and he shot him in that church
He goes and he had that smile. It was like the best
Did you ever see a G.I. Jane?
No, well,
if you're talking about like cartoon shit, then yeah, but if you're talking
about like real action, action, action,
who had to G.I. Jane?
That was like 30 years ago.
G.I. Jane.
Oh, I don't want to sell it.
I go all over the map.
Yep, I like it like fast times at Richmond. Hi. Oh my god. Stop it, right?
You dick
Big Cole
Spakoli the best present movie is prison break prison break was a show you dork and I love that break is super corny
Remember, wait, are you talking about the one where the guy has a tattoo all over his body?
Yeah, he has like the entire fucking prison tattooed on his back so he can break his brother out.
Yeah, yeah, that was good stuff.
No, listen, some of these shows.
I'm gonna say this some of these shows are not meant to be like binged watch because they just make the character seem crazy
I'll give you a perfect example
When I was in bed or not even a kid when I was a teenager
I watched through Sons of Anarchy love Sons of Anarchy
But then if you watch Sons of Anarchy like on a binge like if you go like episode by episode by episode
It makes the fucking main character look like a serial killer
You know what I mean like he's just killing so many people all the time
But if you watched it like as it came out like every Monday
as it was supposed to be watched, it doesn't look that crazy.
Right, right.
But if you watch this, if you watch this,
you're back to make Jack looks like a serial killer.
He kills so many fucking people.
Did you? I think after three, you consider a serial killer, right?
I think after three murder, this was on.
This is I think she thinks he's white.
If I'm not white, then what the fuck am I?
Hey, do you listen did you see it was on Apple TV, but it was a couple years ago
I really got addicted and it was kind of one of those it was that called the severance
No, oh, you missed it. That was really good
Yeah, I know that's the other thing too. Like there's so much shit to watch
Like I go down a rabbit hole and then they have this what do you call clickbait?
Or here's this picture of like this like you know, and I and then of course all the body cam shit
It's like, you know, everybody's like knocking on someone's door. Then I got addicted for a while to the evictions
I know that's sick, but like watching the people like it evicted
You know me were they knocking the door? I mean, I got evicted. I just left. I was not trying to
I left way before the fucking sheriff was gonna come in yeah. Oh, no, I'm not I'm not going through that fuck that right right
No, I wouldn't want yeah
Nope
Yeah, that's crazy
Sheriff's coming to you like what I
Don't know just pay your fucking rent or your mortgage and no one happened. I mean, it's pretty simple
Yeah, but sometimes you're young and you're stupid
Did you do any of the 80s movies of the John Hughes movies?
Did you watch any of that?
Like 16 K-Ball?
I've played Dyer and Breakfast Club.
Breakfast Club, yes.
Yeah, Breakfast Club, yes.
And then there was a couple of 16 candles Uncle Buck. Oh my god. That's so good
Well, I know I've never actually seen that movie, but I always
I feel like that's the only John Hughes movie. I haven't seen at this point, right?
And then the way trees and automobiles. Oh my god, that's my favorite. Yeah, that's so fucking funny
Oh, there's spies like us fucking spies like us Steve Martin, right Steve Martin pulp fiction
Is Steve Martin still alive?
Yes.
How?
Because it has been 70 for 60 years.
It's okay.
I know he's still alive.
He has some big nose.
He has white hair my entire life.
Yes.
Some people have white hair when they're young.
The Griswold's Chevy Chase.
The Griswold, the wash, the vacation.
Chevy Chase is still alive too, I think, right?
Like, well, fuck, how?
There was another farm that was really funny too.
Motherfucker was like long in the East.
Yeah, it was cherry chase bill. How are you holding in the 80s and you're still alive?
What it did how you bought it in the 80s. It's still alive. See this is like
He's true
It's about that time we bring up the meat. You know what it is cute. They have money
That's what it is, bro.
What about Mike and Jonathan?
He's kind of, he's still alive.
Mark Campbell was a baby in the 80s.
Obviously, he's just still alive,
but some of these people were old as fuck in the 80s.
They're like 40 in the 80s and they're still alive.
They're relieved they haven't failed you some time.
I mean, fucking Sammy the Bull is still alive for Christ's sakes.
But how the fuck did Sammy the Bull live to be 83
and then become a fucking YouTuber?
Like, I just, it doesn't make any sense.
I never thought I would live the day to see like fucking old New York fucking mobsters arguing on YouTube
That one, okay, let's slip to the 90s. What about as good as it gets with Jack Nicholson?
Very funny. Who's Jack Nicholson?
Don't know
Yo, he's so young no way that's the point he's never heard. He's either truly
Psycho
Like he was like no, that's Jack Nicklaus
Did you, yeah, did you like it or the water boy? Wait, is it water boy?
That's Adam Sandler. Yeah, that was the best movie ever.
Dude, honestly, you know what's super underrated? My favorite movie with fucking Jack Nicholson is, uh...
Departed?
Is...
No, it's, you'll never guess it, it's with, it's, it's Morgan Freeman, it's called The Bucket List.
Oh, that's my favorite, I love that.
I love The Bucket List.
It's a bucket list.
A big good man with Tom Cruise and Jack, and he's the bucket list.
And he's never seen The Bucket List with Morgan Freeman and Jack Nicholson.
He's in the hospital, he's got cancer, wait, let me like, let me break it down.
And it's like a hospital room, you know, where the curtain splits the two.
And this one guy's like, like Bukku Bucks, which is Jack Nicholson, right?
And he's laying up in the bed, he's got like cancer or something.
Morgan Freeman that's our bit. I don't know one's got something one's got something sub and while they're in there
He starts talking one line. I always in
Psycho know this I always want I if you watch a movie and you remember one set and sometimes it sticks in your head
I always if you know me, I some of my the way I talk
I'll say it's like smoke through a keyhole and remember and now it's cute
Just go with me remember he was telling the story about like when you dream or something happens
You wake up and you know how you're dreaming and you know your dream will vivid and like
You have to get up and go pee or something, right?
Your REM, whatever gets disturbed,
and it's like a vivid dream.
You're like, fuck, was that real?
And then all of a sudden, as soon as you get up
and start thinking about it,
it's like smoke through a keyhole.
I always use that word.
Yeah, hard to remember, right?
Right, right, right.
But in that, yeah, that was the best.
You're skipping out of your mind,
like the smoke is like slipping out through the keyhole.
And when I say keyhole,
like an old school, like in an old,
like let's say New York or one of the movies,
like it's like that skeleton like movie,
like that shaped keyhole.
school like that
That's like such a good that's just such a
I'll feel good moving for me
I just love watching that
Even if you can be having a bad day
You want a fucking whore
Thank you
You gotta make a song of smoke through a keyhole
It makes you appreciate even the small things in life
Don't like you don't you like love the last scene at the very end when he passed away in his last week
Remember here? They're the yellow legal pet. They were like scrambles each one and at the very last
They have like the old school or it's like a cheap coffee chuck full of knuckles
You know I'm talking about that coffee and a can and they put his urn up on the top of that mountain
Well, that was his last wish. You know what I'm talking about the last scene in that
Yep, that was cool. That was fucking cool. You know people remember the movie whenever they like actually go and start doing crazy shit
Like yeah, he took him to go a good driving
And then he like fucking took him skydiving and shit cuz I didn't had all the money. It was so great so fucking great
Yeah, Jack Nicholson's character had like all the they were like the um, like the antithesis of each other like Jack Nicholson's character had all the money but he had he was like
He was like he was like uh, he had like no soul base that he was
Right.
You know, he was like a, he's a shallow hurt that works a bunch of money.
And then Morgan Freeman was like a guy who had a, had a family, the family, normal guy.
Right.
And then, you know what the sad part is?
And then when Morgan Freeman like got out and he was with his wife and she goes to
put on a negligee or something, he comes out and remember, and he's all ready to go.
Like when he, you know, and then he like, he's.
Passes out on the ground remember that I'm not let's say a bad thing
But but it just went he was teaching the one that had all the money with no soul, right?
And like a like a mean cocky bastard. Yeah, he basically showed him how to be
His daughter remember he didn't see his daughter and one of his wishes yet the very end. Yes. Yeah
Plot points and he met his grand kid. Yep
Oh my god, Q after all see who knew? Yeah
Oh
What 20 years in the service can't get promoted look who it is
How long is it gonna take before it's like he gets in the mood for this motherfucker?
Okay, at least we got him laughing.
Literally, it's not long enough because I just roasted this little bitch's ass.
I know, it's only gonna take a long, maybe a couple weeks.
That's why he became an NYPD officer because he's a pussy.
He did the same thing all the time.
But he didn't make the cut for the statroopers, though.
That's what he stands for.
He didn't make the NYSP cut.
We'll made it to the N.Y.P.D. with his fucking shitty G.E. because he's retarded.
I would sell out to you, Alexander.
You're all proud of you.
Keep serving your country, faggot.
Thank you, police.
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle.
Wiggle.
We're having such a good time with our movie ish.
I know and then it's like you had to let this other fucking homosexual on the phone
He doesn't like me so he's attacking me now. He's ruining the party. He's like he invited someone to the party
He doesn't like McQuinn and he can't control himself.
Alexander, why don't you just look for like a fucked up staircase
and just trip and smash your knee and then we can retire you to your pension.
Oh my god, I can't take it.
You don't have to get shot.
I just found a bit of breakthrough.
I know Popsack got shot in a good fashion.
You don't have to go that far.
Go ahead, baby.
Out!
You're right here.
Take out!
Out!
Oh
Somebody like that know so much about life whatever the
Entire like the majority of your adult life was spent on fucking stream yard panels
How do you know so much about anything you've been on stream yard panels since you were fucking 19 years old
That's all you fucking do dork
Yep.
Exactly.
So Mr. McQueen, do you ever watch, I don't know, we're talking about old movies.
So this might be the 60s, it was in color, like you said, you didn't like black and white.
Nope. Oh my god, that's with Elizabeth Paul Newman. I'm the pride baby. That's what we're gonna go
We can then together in a nice little cottage, you know, in the snow under the cover
You can run me through all these movies all the movies some of the even yeah, he wants to get under a hot warm cover with you
Hiding that he's gay
He's not gay
That's a woman
Wait, you have a car?
Hiding that you're gay
Oh, okay. I'm hiding him because I want to join you. No, he's smart
So listen
Wait, Rodi Steen before I leave I want to ask you a question about mr. Below. You're not leaving. I'm leaving
I'm leaving. No, I'm leaving. No, you know I'm leaving first. No, I'm leaving first. No, wait, wait, wait
I want to talk about mr. Bo
Oh my god, he just pulled a note. He just pulled like a nose hair out when he did that out that hurt
Out of Blanca because of Blanca is good. There's a I love old movies. No, I like some of the old black and whites, too
Like a baby a baby Jane. Oh, yeah
Right when she goes blanche if I could get out of this chair and remember when she put like the dead bird. Oh my god
That was such a good movie. Oh my god. Oh my god. Yeah. I used to watch that all the time
Rosemary's baby.
Uh-oh.
Just shh.
Don't hold on.
Rosemary's baby.
Why don't you?
Are you going to let the retarded Puerto Rican up here?
Let's see.
No, who you know, they were target Puerto Rican
He's crying for a link right now in chat
He just wants to come up and cry
I think you should just to let him make himself look stupid because that's really what all he's good for at this point
Is making himself more hated
Okay, that's all day man does he goes around and everybody just hates him more and more the more they fucking see him and have to listen to him
So just let him up here and fucking let him cry. Let him make himself more hated
Have you ever been saman joining?
Uh, who no, I don't think so antithesis of a fucking
You know what?
Yeah, so many good movies. They don't make them like these. I guess
Let me think. Oh my god. I'm so like I'm not me. Okay. So you want to cry about people coming
over to psyche's panel? Literally, all your content is using psyche. So what's so what's
what's the big difference between going to psyche's panel and you literally sitting there for two
fucking hours and watching his stream? What's crazier? Exactly. Yeah. Like, do you think that
You can't think that right?
No, you can't think that we're all as stupid as you are you stupid fucking
You know what everyone loves him because they're everyone's smarter than no everyone doesn't love him
You should see whenever he joins a stream you should you ever seen the chat when he joins a stream now
People watch his stream because he's like the drama hub center thing. That's why he
Yes, I'll have like 90 viewers and three people typing in chat like don't get yourself mistaken here
Oh my gosh. Yeah, there's easy. Hi easy. Is it's miles here? Oh, yeah
So stay triggered. I'm reading the chat now. They like Blair witch project
That was really scary with that first one when it came out
I saw it in the theaters when it came out, but I already knew it wasn't right. Oh, it wasn't that scary to me
Say man, you shouldn't be so worried about me. You should be worried about finding out who your dad is
Yeah, you don't know your father. I
Mean fuck
My parents are dead, but at least I knew who they were
Sam you don't know your dad. I know this is I know that's something that eats you up inside every day that you don't know
Who your fucking father was you need to go? You know, we have the internet
Ancestry you can probably get one of your stupid fucking handlers to find your father for you
Kate was roasting Sam Anthony. She was like playing him like buying you Geo cards and he was like find your daddy
And he had a different voice. They said that maybe you don't want to find them because then you know
There'd be some evidence of why you look the way you do. Oh, wait. No, that's because you're ugly fucking mother. Sorry
Well, yeah, he was buying you Joe cards and his voice was yeah, I know his mother was ugly
He had it. Oh, I just thought of another movie. That was one of those twisty long ones ready
The usual suspects
Is that a fish called Wanda's the sequel to it? No, this is ahead. I don't know you may not like it
Never mind. Don't worry. It's just
Don't he asked me. What's the question mr. Baloney? I
I want to ask it's have you been back, you know the little grave by the tree have you been back there?
Yeah, okay, so I wanted I want I think it's I know you don't want one because it won't be another mr. Baloney
But they'll be kind of another one and I want you to go and I'll I could try to figure it out
Before the timing was right. That was a long time ago, but like I want you to get another
I need one don't I
And you can you know that for an AI so yeah, I joined the membership three years of mornings enough. Do you tell me?
Uh-huh. Yeah. Yeah, it's time
Yeah, because I yeah, I know you don't want to go through it again and everything but you need that you really a good guy
I do
I just don't I don't know
But I told you that sometimes they come back, you know
It likes I like get sent or nudged or come back if you open yourself up
Right. Yeah, psyche paid me to come on here and trash you Sam. No, I'm talking about as dog
That's how you know how stupid he is like
He's not gonna pay anybody to go on panel and do anything like how stupid are you you fucking retard?
Thank you support anybody to do shit
You know what it is Tony? I think what to my next mr. Baloney's the so-so love on the planet
You know Mr. Bologna. Yes, there's gonna be a Mr. Bologna part two
Part two for dance. You might even want to you might even I don't know if you want to calm Bologna 2.0, but
Maybe call me since you always
No, we'll do a Roni. I'd love you to call your dog Roni. That would be great
You really I really that's a great name. We're already manifesting it as we go
Alex, what are your thoughts on Crown Heights?
Crown Heights, Brooklyn. So it's a bunch of put me on the pussy's
New York live crown Heights
That's what it's called. No, you're 100% right. You're 100% 100% that's pussy heights. It should be called pussy
I've never met a real n-word from there. They're always pussy. Oh, bro. They're the biggest pussies are out there and crimes
Me too
I do.
That was the best response ever.
That was such a good response.
What the fuck?
Me too.
I'm gonna say, baby, the truth.
All I say is the truth.
I do.
I smack them all in crying.
So, man, speaking of it, I'm gonna have to schedule some smacking tomorrow.
We'll have this tomorrow.
What does that mean, smacking tomorrow?
I'm gonna go to crime. I said smack people. I got you. I got you
You know what I do and I don't understand people and we don't believe the same I find one thing we have in common
I don't even get like somewhere to break bread together
Anything like like that guy over there
They're both groomers. I bet you could find in common with that guy that Sam in
Yes, we're both men there. Okay. There you are
We cook poppies
We're both we're both males with penises. He's not man. Okay
to
What else I can't come from that I never put his pants down
But he sits down when he tastes pisses so we came really really there
How do I know are you kidding?
He obviously takes piss to sitting down
You do not sit down on toilet board that's for women if you sit down to pee
That's not a man a man pushes dick out and pisses in the toilet
Holds himself against the wall with one hand, you know, you know fucking horses cock. You don't stay down
So that's crazy. My head is full of like cartoon visuals
On the toilet dangling I get so many fucking visuals
Hey, Joanie Baloney. Yes, sir. How many live laugh love signs do you have in your house?
Oh, I don't have any of them really. I do have one that says good vibes. That's a fluorescent that stays on
But bubby it's in cursive for reals. Yep
And I have lights on here around I get like like over the fireplace right now
I'm looking at I have white lights all the way my balcony has lights drift
I gotta have lights. I have electrical fireplaces like right now. I'm looking at it. Yeah, most humans normally do have to have lights
That's kind of how we exist. I got ambience. I got five salt. It's not funny though that we have a natural light the Sun
Like he comes up in the morning. Yeah, but you need a light when there is no sun
No, isn't that crazy that the Sun comes up one time a day
That's crazy
It's fucking insane, what is that thing you
It's a big fucking fireball like a thousand miles away. Listen, a thousand miles away
A thousand miles away, Florida more like a
Way dick 10 billion
Anyway, it's a stupid not light bulb. It comes up in the morning like thing wake up and then it goes down
They go to bed. It's just
Someone made that shit
Reddit
Joni is a regular at less panel chat. What's that?
What's a less
You don't know what that is, Joni. Don't play stupid. Don't play stupid. You're getting exposed to it.
I have no idea what that is. Seriously.
No, she's a she's a confidential informant. She's here to fuck around with us for some other panel.
Oh, I see.
Then you think that is 150 million kilometers
this guy's like a thousand miles away.
She's in Whitton saved.
I got I got a hunt.
I got to do the money.
I got a lava lamp.
I've never turned them off three years now.
Wait, let me count one, two, three, four.
I haven't had a lava lamp since high school.
I got seven.
You would kill for a lava lamp.
They're not that worth it.
Bullshit.
I know, but that's one day you don't
I still love my love
Yeah, you know much. I fuck with those lava lamp
Not like I got one lava lamp
Remember the ball you touched and the lightning like hit your fingers
There was a dumb like little crystal ball. Remember that. Did you guys have that the lightning ball? I don't know, but I get
I don't know. These salt lamps are supposed to be anti-anxiety. They ain't working, but I like it.
They're standing in the chat.
You're the new favorite Jew.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, seriously, I'm done with this baby. I'm done with Johnny but only tonight and anointed one.
Do you like it in the ass bitch? End of story because you're talking my kind of my language
Anointing when you said anointing you know what I thought of oil oil and I'm gonna anoint that ass
That's why that's what you you put upon yourself with the anointing the ass cheeks
like
Yeah, you see that well you're gonna take seven
Okay, and you're forgiven
I'm kissing this poor lady and then he decided to fuck her in the ass.
You're forgiven, James.
What the fuck?
I mean, I don't know what to do.
I just, like, brought a cross and now I'm, like, burying it real quick.
Are you even willing to protect her?
Hugh, help me out here with this lunatic.
Seriously, bro, I'm not ready for...
Wait a minute.
I'm, like, used to hearing the good guy.
No, no, no.
Hugh, I'm calling back up, bro.
I'm honestly...
She loves you, Alex.
I mean, back up.
I'll call whiskey.
I said the anointing, I was teaching you, anointing, not an ointment, an anointing, you sicko.
Yo, yo, it's like he's sitting up there, he's like, why the fuck is he saying that?
It's licking your asshole and then fucking it, that's all you're bringing to my mind right now,
you anointing dog.
I was doing body of Christ
The talk of Christ compose you open that pussy bitch. We're gonna exercise this fucking tonight. We're gonna exercise the demon
He wants the exercise to come on let's do it fuck it
Wait, bring me my armor. Bring me my armor. Fuck it. It's game on tonight. May the power of Christ
compel you. May the power of my queen's talk compel you. May the power of my queen's talk compel
you. No, stop it. You can't do that. You can't say what you say and get away with it. You might
end late. Yes, I can. You might have to go in the basement. Yo, psyche. Psyche, okay? Psyche's
levitating right now and spinning around. No one notice. Psyche's levitating and spinning in midair.
The demon is working baby over time.
No, he doesn't have any McDonald's money right now, motherfucker.
Yeah, he's twitching, he's having a Big Mac withdrawal.
Like a Big Mac win.
The demon.
Oh my god, stop it.
Someone get this guy a coffee before he does his head.
Fuck in space, 360 degrees.
I'm about to get this guy a coffee.
Oh my god, I can't do it.
The power of my talk and my credit card can power you.
I
Yeah, no, you settle baby. Not everybody knew
Yeah, you got Johnny Bellini over here fucking crying laughing
Abort listen to me listen now you look here look all right strap it down boy strap it down
Obviously just get the chair. We're gonna strap her down
I'm dying right now.
You get the legs, the inside to get the hands.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait, wait.
I don't want to talk.
I was talking about I was talking about Unleavened Bread
or whatever that wafer and you took that
and went to write to the exercises and said levitate.
I see how you crisscrossed.
Crisscrossed was an American rap band in the 80s.
There is close remember it was a little black
All right, that's enough
It is enough see when she is black. It's over
Hey wake up. He's on like six panels at the same time
You don't know sick by now
We come see you're on the air. Oh, please sister
Hmm, don't I mean, this is one of the ugliest human beings
That's probably ever walked a face of the earth
The guy has to join as many panels as he possibly can otherwise will never get in anywhere
Exactly say goes to a haunted house and he comes out with a fucking job application
You understand no he doesn't come out with a job location. He comes out employed
Like, oh my god.
No, you're higher on the spot.
I'm looking for a better picture now, leaving.
Because I don't like SIG.
I genuinely think he's one of the ugliest, weirdest-looking niggas I've ever seen in
my entire life.
Who that dude is?
He literally looks like fucking he looks like Squidward's house like this shit is crazy
He's got the same nose that's Squidward Mexican Squidward 100% you just know
He's balding now.
No, he's not good.
So ugly. I swear to God, I've never seen
a person that's fucking ugly.
And that is an ugly motherfucker right there.
OK, that's one of the he looks like a piece of shit.
Like, no, literally like a turd.
Okay, well
Yeah, jeez you want to come up here and fight me bitch. Oh, sorry. I say that I'm sorry
I mean that guy is fucking I
Just get sometimes I can't get over how fucking ugly. Yes
It's like it's like God. It's like God was pissed off at me people. I decided to make one really fucking ugly
Every time I see him, I don't sleep for two days.
Oh, let's make this Mexican look like a fucking Incan.
Whoa, Joey.
They made you look like an Incan.
He looks like an Incan.
He did it to me.
No, I'm not talking to her.
I'm talking to him.
Looks like an Oompa Loompa Inca from hell.
Like an Indian Oompa Loompa.
Pick him up.
Rank him up.
There's rain in the chat.
All right.
Rain's cool.
I think she was talking to her.
That's sexy.
No, something else.
You're talking to the, what's their name?
and
my friends my ribs are still hurting i you guys i just cracked three ribs of that five
minutes session i'm gonna call up easy and have cracked the rest of your ribs there you go
do what you gotta do go but make it count speaking of i'm gonna tell him i'm gonna tell him uh i'm
gonna tell him there's so much you're living in pounds while he's wounded he's a wounded animal get
Okay
Give me kisses, give me kisses, Joni. That's the only thing that can
Help me ribs extension
You made me you really made me laugh so hard. I don't know why I mean I want to be mad at you
But I can't you the way you say stuff is the way you come in and you just somebody stop me like Jim Carrey and masks
It's ridiculous. You can throw yourself out there and it's just so
It's you know, you're joining. So when did you start going through menopause?
Oh cute, it doesn't matter. That makes her better. That means she can't get pregnant anymore, but she can still fucking come.
Hopefully you can just shoot up the club all you want.
After menopause, it's like...
You can just shoot up the club all you want, huh?
I can come in her old day and no babies. That's awesome. Now we're talking.
Come.
It's like you're not getting nothing from you. You can get come in all day and you won't have any babies either.
Oh my god
Everybody's
Not everybody
Pray ate them for dinner. I would have to thank you. You're gonna come in someone one day
No, baby. You left me. Oh, no, maybe I heard last night. Shut up
Your last night. I might have a baby
Oh, please listen, I know that I'm really good looking but you don't listen my jeans are I'm saving them
Our baby would be so cute you it would be like no no
It might have some of my jeans, but it probably looks like a fucking crackhead at the end of the day
Wait, you're like you're having a baby. I mean if I if we did have a baby it looked like a crackhead like him. Oh
Hmm, but it would be a beautiful hair. I would crack it with beautiful. No, oh my god
And me and Johnny had a baby will look like starting John probably
That will be a baby boy
You know that movie you were just talking about planes trains and automobiles
Yeah.
Did you see that one?
Yeah, it was like an hour ago.
He came out and the one guy.
Right.
That's okay.
Exactly.
What's wrong?
There's no such thing as time and space.
Direct.
No.
The guy came up in the pickup to pick them up, remember?
And it was a guy.
He comes out of this funny old like what I'm, okay, never mind.
I won't say it.
Never mind.
So what the fuck was the boy doing that you have to say now?
He came out and he goes, are you here to give us a ride?
And Steve Martin was like real proper,
and then there was John Candy, right?
And they're sitting on their suitcases,
and they're like freezing, and they're
out in the middle of nowhere.
And this guy come up, he goes, I'm a cousin of somebody.
And it's this guy, this little guy,
and he spits on the ground.
And it's so funny and then he and then he they go he goes the lady the lady
It's like in the his woman or his wife gets out of the truck and
And and like he goes pick up their their luggage and they if he says something like they go
Oh, no, no, no, that's okay, and they go
Don't worry, she gave she had birth and gave her the baby came out five ways.
It was really funny.
Sorry, never mind.
Sorry. That's funny.
But why is everybody from New York City fucking gay?
I don't know.
I've never been to New York.
I know most of the people not in New York.
I'm talking about New York City.
Most of them are fucking gay weirdos.
Oh, come on.
No, seriously, they are.
I know say I was a gay weirdo, and he's fucking a pedophile
Stop talking about PDF
That's too much
I'm talking about New York City. Not that I get it
But we're laughing and then we went right to that. Yeah, well, we can talk about it
I just want to know why they're all gay. There's a great movie
Tony not fat
Yes. Who's there?
Nothing.
Who's there?
Hotch.
Even controller admitted to eating pussy before.
Oh my God.
I told you they're gay.
You ruined the joke by saying controller, but it's okay.
Nothing.
is that she's from your city so you have to accept her in 20 years
it's like a natural
she's from Staten Island
there you go
there you go, do the Tyronys
hachoo
look, Controla's
what do you call a pig that owns Kung Fu?
one of Controla's six dads was in the mafia
okay, so you gotta respect that life
don't that fat pig
ugh
Control her. Wow. Why are you getting the dark on us? Damn. Damn
Control you're making sure you're making a journey. I don't even know what you wanted was talking her
And she won
they were stuck or she said they were stuck
so he she put Zaya in court like literally real life court
yeah but nobody nobody won basically the judge just said like
to the base of the charges
she went there to try to get a restraining order on Zaya
and the judge basically said like i'm not going to grant you a restraining order based on this
but then he said to Zaya like stop fucking around or else it's going to get more serious so
most accusations to try to get it
because he saw it and he go to near her house or buy her kids' school or something.
Yeah, that's not enough. Yeah, he drove past, he drove past, uh, he drove past,
control his kids' school and shouted out, I love you, Ellie, like her kid's name. It was,
it was bad. That's not enough to get her restraining order. You have to prove to the judge that your
life is in danger. You have to make him believe.
That your life is in danger. You have to actually show him like my boyfriend's insane
I need restraining order because he did this this and that like
Yeah
You're gonna prove to the judge that you're scared for your life basically you have to sell it you have to lie to the motherfucker like I'm
She's like running in her sleep. She's like her
You know, what's this guy's day is deal though, but she's what's his deal? What's this deal?
So him and peps are a couple and why does everyone hate them?
Because he's I don't know because one of them is a pedophile and the other one abused their child
I mean, well, they technically they are both child abusers
One is a pedophile the other one is also a dog abuser as well
She left her dog in her fucking hot-ass apartment in Florida
Where it was like a hundred degrees in the summer with no AC on because she got evicted so she just left the dog there
like pebs is like it
Some of these people that the shica has gone on it was like three two or three years ago people just forget
You know, they don't care anymore
So whenever you see pebs on a panel, just remember that she shoved pills down her kids
throat. This is this is from CPS, not me.
And she abused a dog.
She's a scumbag.
So just remember that whenever you see these people that these like fucking
faggot niggers try to fucking.
Stop. That's what they do.
Don't use those words.
the
I just don't so he doesn't support those people. I don't know
I don't know the stories. Pets needs to worry about brushing her tongue once in a while with all the fucking
facts building how they how I might interact with them just like he said she doesn't judge them on what everyone says because there's a lot of stories
Yeah, thank you. Your camera is really fucking blurry, dog. Put your like wipe it off or something
Or maybe like maybe it's the focus is fucked up. Maybe it is
to do I didn't ask you to lick the camera, Dork
and his hair is getting so long, look at that shit
there you go, it's weird
what are you going for, psyche, down to your ass, your nipples, what's the hair stopping
when are you gonna have to do it
I'm only gonna cut it when somebody donates for, you know, have a josey bear haircut, that'll be
no, no, no, but it's coming, I can make you into people long time
crazy that like you
When I first came across you, which was like maybe a year and some change ago,
your hair was shorter than mine.
And so your hair has grown longer than mine.
And I've been growing my hair for like fucking four years now.
And like, how does, I don't understand how some people's hair just like grows
that fast.
Like mine gets to a certain point and then just like stops.
I have a good, I have very good genes.
I don't have my hair got past my shoulders now, and I can't get it any longer
It doesn't seem like it gets any fucking longer than what it is. I I've been I've been at the same length for like a year
Mm-hmm. I love your hair. Your hair looks great
I'm like I'm listening and then I look to the right and I'm just going mm-hmm like good tennis game
Yeah, 40 love 40 love 40 love
Right
i mean i'm just saying it's it's no i'm listening i like a good like you know back and forth
it's interesting i don't know but i can only imagine what she's supposed to say
i don't want to hear nothing out of your whore mouth to be honest with you
because you still don't even acknowledge that scolund isn't a fucking out of tree so i don't
hear nothing out of you
All right, that's how that's how it's dirty
She's Scottish she lives in Scotland, but she won't acknowledge that Scotland is not a fucking country
Yeah, she does classy pig bitches Scottish dickhead
Oh, I thought you meant Joanie.
No.
Wait, what?
I got to apply to Scotland to find her?
I'm confused.
Joanie, you're looking at Arizona.
I'm excited.
What do you want from my life?
No, Q, don't scare me like that.
Alright, we're talking about some other bitch.
I don't care.
Joanie, you're domestic, right?
I'm domesticated.
I've been going out with fucking classy about new shit since like 2022.
The classy sassy or yeah, it's a classy pig bitch pee-pee classy
I'll sing showy. Let's all sing a song showy. Yeah, what do you want to sing guys? Um, I want to say
This land is my land
I can't
You can't help me, Lord, I can't change, Won't you find me, free, back here?
Sorry, don't be sorry. Don't be sorry, baby
Sorry, oh my god, I know that voice from somewhere
This is the Lisa Jordana, bro
No
No, no, you're Lisa I just heard it you sound just like you when she's
That's you I knew it. I knew it
How long did you think you could keep it from me?
Ronys, it's Joni and Lisa. Yes, Alex. No, I believe it's Ronys. Alex, do you realize that you thought you thought ghosts?
I just heard the little
You thought you thought ghost was allied master computer for two years
Here for that
You've been listening
me anymore you guys enough of this shit so what do you want me and what I've been around here a
lot longer than you have anyone you can't fool me and word yeah look it's psyche looking like
fucking Jesus Christ and fucking Benny Benny Brad at the same time it looks like Benny Jesus
I want to get I want to get a perm and I'll thank you
Oh my gosh, I don't have a perm
I need to get one if I wanted to my hair really here. I don't have a naturally curly hair. Okay, I would
It's called head and shoulders just wash your hair with shampoo once in a while, I might get curly psyche
Maybe just wash your hair
I've watched it. It's like a wash. It's cold. That's who my man. If you don't look good, we don't look good.
our
Came in like a water
Come on, Johnny. Keep singing baby. Keep singing to me
Don't keep singing to him. He's gonna start busting
He's just asking you to keep singing
Peace
Bust a nut.
Bust a nut, cruel.
Okay, I'm sorry.
All right. Everybody go to their corners. Are we done?
Yeah
Come on out touch the tip of my glove and go back. Let's go. Yeah, Johnny Baloney. Have you ever Johnny Baloney?
Have you ever stuck two dicks at once? Wow
Yeah
You definitely have yeah, I mean you won 100% have
The fifth I have not sir. Did you make them touch tips?
You have your touch tips tips. No, I've never touched your
My penis. Are you having okay? Have you ever been a little tells no, no, I have not taken no no won't be
No, no
Anything with touching tips is called docking
So they touch tips and the guy that's on circumcised puts their flat over the other car and they
Which is kind of hard because everybody's fucking circumcised
So have you redocked before you
You are
I am cut here. You're gonna dock with psyche one day when you meet them. You're gonna dock. Are you on circumcised psyche?
I mean if you were on circumcised I couldn't imagine
Megma you have built that means you just got rosebeam pussy
The roast you have roaches in your foreskin if you were uncut
Pussy you got a hunt for like the pussy you gotta move all this shit aside all this mean now that's enough
You make a sandwich and lettuce tomato on the way
Johnny Johnny
As a woman like do you do you prefer, you know circumcised or uncircumcised
circumcised
Most why it doesn't make a difference. It's still a cop. That doesn't make a difference. Are you kidding?
Oh, no, I don't need that ludge. I don't need that ludge.
It makes a difference when a girl is sucking your dick. Oh
I don't know
I don't like my mushroom sauté
care which cock you suck whether it has four skin or not. We get that.
Well, can you explain to her that it makes no difference?
Guys, I just opened his page. It says, watch where you cut. And it says it's four skin.
Does the circumcision of male children is ritually required? Oh, no.
and has been common among the religious oh you and you always have to bring the
historic part a little bit of fun in the hair and
your fucking sacroella instead of Ronnie's like what
circumcision is very common amongst Catholics as well as Jesus so that's why
i'm like i don't believe psychist news is real
i just know it's too it's too much of a no to me
I'm definitely fucking glad they chose to circumcise me though because there's a lot of women who don't like fucking uncut dicks, so
Oh brain is running into a skull. Can you give her?
I don't listen to everything women's day imagine if I did that
Oops I echoed what happened
All right, that's okay everybody. I'm sorry
You have worse skin won't be safe. Yeah, it's okay. Wait, what happened? What's okay? Let me look at the chip
Yeah, we're skin. Oh, he does. Yeah. Okay. Is that good? Is it good for you?
I'm gonna leave again because weird things happen when I leave. Let's see what happens. I'm not judging. I don't know I
Mean the moon it takes gonna pop up. Get ready. I'll look at him with the little he says I keep it clean
So then it's good. He loves it
Acting like he has anything better to do
I'm curious about it. Send me a picture, hun.
Do is that cure for Quincy? What was the cure about? I believe you won't be saying my first
Why do you 45 no way get the fuck out of here, bro. Don't tell me it's that simple
Because my
Geez, that was a thick and what? Oh, I think in girthy. Okay. Oh, but then someone else says you have a micro fallow
No, that's the funniest thing I've ever heard. My first car was a Q45
Where's how many other motherfuckers first car was a Q45?
No, Q45 was actually the top of the line. I recall
Another cute. Well the black dog of what?
No, the big dog of the infinity line
Infinity yeah, it was the big boy, but I had a
I was like having the 88 or like the s-class
I was too young at the time I was too young at the time to know how to take care
But how'd you get that selling drugs your fucking pay parents how'd you get a q45 at that early age?
He named himself Alex was like it was only eight grand. Oh my god, it's four fifteen in the morning
Okay, bye
215 here, so shut up. I know right
For Alex, I know I deleted it. I deleted the numbers. Okay. Who I didn't know what that was. I'm busy looking your words are crying
I got a fucking work. That's a that should be to me
I gotta be a one police officer. No, and you guys are bitching. Oh
Be good, I gotta go
Oh
The thing about Joanie is is that she has to stay here until I leave. Otherwise, I'm gonna send concrete to her house
Hey, you are not
Quick create don't even joke about it Zaddy. I miss when you would be in Speedos. Oh my god
That's not funny
Can we kick one of the women off the one that's on the bottom? Yes. Thank you
Can can I am something that's like what's really weird right now you want to know
There is a bird outside my choice
Yes, I love the more why is the bird sleeping by my door because the dark they like to see no, but they
Other I'm afraid of bones got that cabin. There was birds everywhere
Why the bird shows you and stuff like that, you know, I saw it. I saw it. I saw it. I saw it
I said I posted one just so weird it like I'm wondering are they sitting on the eggs or the babies already hatched
What's going on? He when I look out there. He just just like looking up like like is he sleeping sitting there?
He's not moving. He's sleeping. He's not dead. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. All right
Mean it's like I don't know if there's eggs. I didn't see eggs
Fucking scream really loud and stomp your foot. No, I did that the other day. No, I don't want to don't scare away the bird
No, she tried to the other day psyche didn't work
Well, I was screaming because there was a beat I found a beetle on the ground and I didn't know it was a big black beetle
It was really scary looking. Was it from Iran?
I don't know. I've never seen anything like it. It was like my cat was chasing it. It was big and black
It was like really scary. You know what wait did I just fall so it was like a rob rack beetle
I don't know what it was. It had little viper fingers like on the side a little like little crab fingers. It was weird
So scary
Uh-oh, what's happening here? I don't need it. I don't need it
Richie what?
There's so many speed-flipping phone numbers in the chat. I don't know. What's going on? Oh, yeah, I saw that and I was like
I don't even know what those phone numbers are. I don't know who the fuck
Chow Chow's RQ Martha Stewart has a chow chow. They have blue tongues. They have like blue black
That's Barry in the chat Barry Barry is Kate's
We're a homosexual black man. Yeah
Well, you can you can know the way we know he's black is because of his fucking voice
It's isn't it crazy how you can tell that somebody's a fucking
You know an n-word or a white or a fucking speck just by their voice Wow
Geez no, it's true
Alright, you listen you never seen you never seen what Barry looks like right, but you listen and talk you can tell
That's a fucking black dude. We know he's black. Yeah, we you can you can hear the poverty through his fucking voice. Oh
Okay, okay. Oh cry about it. They've said way worse about me. It's okay. I know okay. I love you. I love you back
Um here was nice chatting with you, bro. You're not welcome here anymore. Oh, yeah, it's okay
No, you're done here. Every time you come up here. I'm gonna talk shit. No, you're not
You're a good lesson you making me stronger. Thank you for teaching me tonight to survive
I'll teach you something moment. I know mo mo fo. Yeah, come on now. I'm saying good night you for real for real
All right. All right, Charlie Brown. Good night, fuckface. Okay. Okay. Goose lips. All right. So
I feel like we're like like in a little cafeteria. We're all like, how do we be pulling my tail? Ow!
So, um, you know, ponytail I meant, you know, um, okay.
So that's it, right? Are we I love you again, and uh, all right. All right, Johnny. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good.
Oh, I get it. Okay. Whoops. I mean, you know, you know, I'm stepping into okay. All right. Bye guys. Good night. Peace out
Love you guys for real for real. All right. All right. I'm going bye
Bye-bye. It's just you and me Q. What do you want to do? Who the fuck was that lady? That's my friend, Joni
She's pretty much you squirt I've never tried anything with her like that. Oh, you should figure it out
And get back to me.
Did you score it?
Yeah, I scored it.
Wow.
Oh, what's up, Q?
Let's get next to you a little bit.
Sorry.
Now I'm just stuck here with your faggot ass. I know but what do you that's just what do you want to do to it?
I'm about that. I'm actually I mean, I'll stay on I'm not leaving the panel
I don't care, but I gotta fucking I gotta eat something before I get asleep and I got a fucking work tomorrow
It's already 2 30 in the fucking morning fuck
Yeah, I technically I have to wake up at 9 so I have you know, I have some hours
My gosh, okay, we'll make yourself some food and I'll be here
To gaze we're not to gaze excuse a straight guy, which I'm very attracted
He wouldn't be as into it if I was gay
Hear that fart
I thought the microphone was better than that
You were gay
So you're a rainbow. I thought you were straight. Oh my god six back. I'm not sick
You have a six pack of fucking ribs
See and that's the greatest thing
I already know what you're saying. You say how does that look? I usually when I join your panel
I put my phone down like and don't even look at it and that's the greatest part
Look at the scene that aren't bullshit. You don't see six sigmens on the panel. Oh
Great. Oh, I'm so happy
See are you okay? What happened? You fell asleep. I was super excited that fucking fuck
I was just throwing up in my mouth a little bit. Why?
Because I am a heterosexual
No, you get out of here. I'm here with you alone. You want a best thing?
Yeah, well see guys a boyfriend him 300 low so he can't
Dude, Sig e-dated a fucking grandma and he might still be e-dating a fucking grandma for like four years
He might still be doing it
I don't know cuz he can never give a straight answer about anything but he's e-dating a fucking grandma
You want to see what she looks like actually I can show you let's see. This is this is some deep lore for you right here
Where is it? Where's that picture at? Oh?
I don't think I have it on here, but I have to ask him about it
Cigar you still did in the old lady yeah dig yeah
So what you're not gonna work in a rose nigga you're mad
Work it he rose work it he rose as you get none. He's talking about your grandmother nigga
Much of a pussy are you getting work greasy ass head?
He's mad that his grandmother
So he's mad about his fucking greasy and you he dated a fucking grandma. I'm not mad about nothing boy
Did you date your you dated beta? I
Think they're the same me. I think you're her and work here. You're like the same age. Oh my god
We're kitty Rose every time this nigga comes up here. Just ask him about work. He rose
Was not oh, I thought he said beat his kid. He wrote nothing, but old ladies. What about it, bitch?
Your grandmother away from me nigga
Yeah, don't say the n-word say you don't have that privilege up here nigga only Q can say it
If your grandmother look like you beat a keeper away from me nigga
Wow, he's so disrespectful
What's wrong with that guy honestly, I don't know. Maybe he's gay
I don't understand
I know you should be more like me. That's your problem
You should be maybe you should be like somewhat as good-looking as me too, and you might get away with more. Yeah
Especially with me
Don't even say for yourself. Yeah, speaking at you motherfucker. You stop letting bring it you up here else
I'm gonna start fucking with you. Oh, you are not
My bet
Don't care if you fuck with me. I like being mistreated. No, I don't think you will like it. I have a fetish
Okay, you get out of here. Well, okay. Well, I will don't threaten me. I will I'm not threatening you
I'm saying that you probably should
You know, it's like he's vengeful so stop
Okay, and I understand the whole uh, you don't want to be told what to do and you don't want to be told
And I get that but there's certain people where
Okay nigger nigger nigger nigger nigger nigger nigger
Okay, well anyway, thanks a lot q i mean you're fucking a bitch stop it
Why would you do that?
Oh my god
Okay
It's a black and mirror
I feel it the whole way trying to go so bold
Yeah, you remember the ones I used to leave crap, but I'm the one with the ring of iron keys, and I don't belong here
I walk through this place like a law in a robe like I own the silence and the echo both baby
I got just to make a feeling disappear keep your lips baptized and poison honey
Cause you can take it, you love the ache of it
I'm gonna go feral, baby I'ma spin you, skin you, till the needles tire
Play you like a slow hem, play you how I desire
I'll keep you turning, turning circles till the fire's gone
Then I'll fade out easy like a sun that never plans to dawn
Yeah, I'll play you like a slow song
Flip back to the pages, tell me
anything's sacred I never caught promises in stone I caught warnings and develop it
you're the first on the stone and we both know I don't stay but you still stepped out with your
mouth open for the rain oh I got ways of losing you clean I'm quicker than the chase you believe
and I'll keep drumming on your heart until I can't tell love from bleeding because you can take it
To the groove camera
Play you like a slow song. I'll play you like a slow song
I'll I'll delete the I'll delete the stream
Yeah
No, I promise